<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Transferreds on My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/transferred/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Transferreds on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/transferred/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/transferred/the-power-of-the-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/transferred/the-power-of-the-truth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;to tell the truth is hard, we all want a nice story, we all want to be insightful and innocent, powerful and truthful. We cannot escape the truth, it will haunt us until we can express it. It will hang out on our shoulder warping and twisting this world around it. If we do not speak our truth then everything will reflect back through the lies we told. We have to opportunity to free ourself, to see through all of it, but it takes a lot of courage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/transferred/to-capture-a-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/transferred/to-capture-a-memory/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;we pull too the screen to re-live our experience.&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;To become ignited by a memory,&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;we yearn into the moment to remember the feeling&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;and seek to recreate it again.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we peel back the experience of a memory it quickly revels itself as our vision for the future. Each step we take, each move we make is based on the memory of where we are going, of what we are doing. There is no present moment, there is only a memory of the past, reflected as a vision for the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/transferred/why-believe-in-other-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/transferred/why-believe-in-other-lives/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;why believe in other life times..?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;not all like times are meant to shine&#xA;some are meant to stay inside&#xA;the ones that shine spent a long time&#xA;inside before they decide to come alive&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the thing that stops us from appreciating our differences,&#xA;the trap that gets us into envy those who came to shine,&#xA;is the illusion of time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we think that we&amp;rsquo;re suppose to do something shiny&#xA;we give credit to the external evidence&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
