<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media on My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/phone-sickness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/phone-sickness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The greatest danger of social media is the power it takes from actual reality. The way it strips existence of its imagined potential. Our imagination is our greatest power and we need it more than ever right now. Our imagination will pull us through this mess, but not like how we have imagined it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The future has let go of the identity that comes from screens. We understand that there is no substance to numbers and likes, and instead we choose participate in the online world because it can free us to go against the ingrained pattern in real life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/sharing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;share a vision inside&#xA;it helps to live into a vision for the future&#xA;by changing the memory of it&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;every move into the future,&#xA;every decision, every action, every desire&#xA;is a reflection of a memory,&#xA;the path we remember to take&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we are born story tellers,&#xA;we live into the story we tell ourselves,&#xA;what we create outside of ourself,&#xA;creates what we become within,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but rather the way our world is speaking to us&#xA;we create a different memory of the past,&#xA;and then we live into a different future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/social-media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;a streams for my dreams,&#xA;the behind the scenes&#xA;a means for the meaning&#xA;a screen for the feeling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the process zine is teaching me how to follow an internal process&#xA;rather than external time.&#xA;I am learning to learn through myself,&#xA;at this point it is letting all my creations free&#xA;letting the shadow expose itself&#xA;all of this feels like Ive just be practising&#xA;becoming. I am learning I don&amp;rsquo;t need to be liked or accepted,&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t need the external approval, its not what I came for&#xA;and its not what I want deep down,&#xA;i want to be free of time,&#xA;to give myself the room for creation to flow through me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/the-invention-of-screens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/the-invention-of-screens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the way screens become popular was through cartoons,&#xA;we created these characters and stories and fell in love with them&#xA;then slowly we started acting like them,&#xA;like the characters in the stories we watched,&#xA;and then slowly we became them,&#xA;characters on screens&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the screens show us what we create&#xA;reflects back into our experience&#xA;we have created a box for us to work for&#xA;a method and way for creativity to exists,&#xA;we need a character,&#xA;we need to play this game on the screen&#xA;to be cool enough to get attention,&#xA;from others,&#xA;be cool enough to get attention from yourself&#xA;to flip the reflection from the characters we became,&#xA;all the versions we took on&#xA;about the way it was suppose to look,&#xA;now we invent ourself out of that&#xA;by sharing and expressing&#xA;a world that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to anyone&#xA;but you,&#xA;we can remember how to take&#xA;responsibility for our life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/the-photo-struggle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/the-photo-struggle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;remember the feeling&#xA;when you try and capture a moment&#xA;and somethings missing&#xA;we want to capture the way it felt&#xA;the feeling can never be fully captured&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;yet we have this urge to capture the moments&#xA;to create a feeling&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the price of the moment has gone up&#xA;the right moment captured has a worth&#xA;a value, a future, a product,&#xA;we can make a living off of capturing moments&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/the-process-zine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/the-process-zine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;there has been something in side me baking,&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;its been life times in the making,&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;this meal that i&amp;rsquo;ve been craving&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;is finally ready for the saying&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the process has been a surface game i invented to play into my inner world, and see where it would take me. This journey took me far off screen and showed me why sharing it and trying to make life real online was taking away from this inner journey. This zine was a deep question inside, if technology could be used to express creativity how would it look? This has been this game to remember. It is not an instagram account, it is an inward timeline, a reflection of my inner experience, and now my inner experience is coming outside of me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/the-search-for-truth---technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/the-search-for-truth---technology/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;what technology is giving us is a direct reflection of self&#xA;we are given all the worlds we could have to reflect our truth,&#xA;in social media we are given a display of the worlds we think are true,&#xA;the worlds we are attracted to, the ones we believe in, the sides we love,&#xA;we follow&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;when technology began it was more a reflection of what technology could do,&#xA;everything was just a display of anything, because no one knew what the internet was for&#xA;slowly became a vessel to discover ourself through,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/the-web/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the internet has a beautiful power,&#xA;to connect us&#xA;gives us endless possibility to interact with the people of our kin,&#xA;our our truth in a new form.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Until now our connection to each other has been hindered by race,&#xA;social group, and religon. Until now we have been connecting to people through a shared beleif systems and social structures from the world around us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The internet has a power to connect us with people of the same truth,&#xA;of the same inner beleif systems, of the same inner worlds,&#xA;but the power of the beast, requires us to learn to tell a new truth,&#xA;a new story to our brothers and sisters,&#xA;one that is of an inner truth,&#xA;a true truth.&#xA;Not of the one the world around us has projected upon us,&#xA;we are made to break the image this world has projected onto itself,&#xA;because it is hurting our souls,&#xA;we are at war,&#xA;fighting our brothers and sisters, about these made up systems,&#xA;about these external games, money, numbers, power, and religion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
