<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/addressing-a-problem/money-power-and-religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/addressing-a-problem/money-power-and-religion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we have been taught and formed&#xA;on the need to think about our world through the frame of numbers&#xA;through money through  time&#xA;we want external guarantee and known outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We believe time is something happening outside of us,&#xA;something that the more we plan it,&#xA;the more we know it,&#xA;the more we can guarantee a numerical outcome,&#xA;the more we can receive from it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;what if the gift of time is not something we can know and plan?&#xA;what if the gift is in the way it reveals itself to us in a process&#xA;through an internal experience with no external prof&#xA;what if all the need to prove our value stops us from the greatest value&#xA;and the greatest value we have is not something that can be shared with anyone&#xA;how does that change your experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/art/slowly-remembering-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/art/slowly-remembering-why/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i don&amp;rsquo;t make art to make art&#xA;its an experiment&#xA;to see if I could trust in time&#xA;to see if I could let my inner world be,&#xA;what would it have to show me&#xA;to see what the creative process had to say when I trusted in it,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;what i learned was, this process did not want to be planned,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;when I surrendered I was given something&#xA;beyond what I could have expected&#xA;the process wants to remain unknown&#xA;when I didn&amp;rsquo;t confine the experience to money or numbers or time,&#xA;It always led me to create a different exchange&#xA;that allowed something much stronger to flow through&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/art/the-tragic-story-of-money-and-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/art/the-tragic-story-of-money-and-art/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I has a classic experience where I saw a wall that looked like it could use a mural and talked to the owner. At first he&amp;rsquo;s super stoked about the idea, we talk about a vision, I show him my previous work, we get the excited about the idea of the art, and then begin to talk logistics. Getting the paint? sure he can pay for it! Then i mention gently, that ive done alot of work for free, and I just cant do that anymore - I should get paid for the work. He agrees, but the entire demeanour of the conversation changes. Now things are serious, now comes the determining factor, will there even be this beautiful imaginary project if the numbers don&amp;rsquo;t make sense. There comes a pause, and my partner and him start talking in Hebrew, I see the man back down saying , loh loh, the translation is no, no in english. The idea is cancelled, a number was mentioned beyond what made sense to the owner and the moments over.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/athens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/athens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the collective is drowning in itself&#xA;everyone must be protective in their shell against the need to be sold,&#xA;in these hotspots, in these places where we have identified as national monument,&#xA;where the collective has collective in a swarm around places,&#xA;where the number of people grew at the same time as the number of business,&#xA;and where you couldn&amp;rsquo;t come around a corner without trying to be sold something&#xA;I was in the heart of where western civilization was born&#xA;I was in the birth place of this idea,&#xA;and it had flipped inward on itself,&#xA;the vendors and the people faced an inward tension and anxiety to swim in a current that was over crowded and everyone had to fight for a spot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/craft-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/craft-club/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;open hours weekly 2-9 Saturdays&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;each week we will have different discussions of creativity and themes which explore various mediums&#xA;supplies and curriculum provided&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;for more information&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;welcome to the creativity club&#xA;each week we will explore a different medium of creativity&#xA;that has an assignment intergated into your week&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the course is to teach us how to live creativity&#xA;and extract and find meaning through ourself and our experience.&#xA;Its time we devote ourself to a bigger world,&#xA;the world inside.&#xA;I beielive the future will lose its trust in this outer world,&#xA;and we will have no choice but to practise creating our own world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/currently/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/currently/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;everything is my world is opposing each other. Ellias contradicts dror. My career fuelled by freedom, contradicts my relationship. I have to explain that for me the future is open, it&amp;rsquo;s an open promise to myself to live each day and see where it takes me. I can not control this request, this was my work, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t fuelled by money it was fuelled by hope. When I made this promise to myself I faced many problems, like not having money, this was hard but as I continued to follow it I never one felt like I wasn&amp;rsquo;t supported by the world. I am proud of myself for not relying on money, I feel ultimately liberated for getting away without it. When I met my partner we wanted to plan the future, he wanted a plan, he did not have the trust I had in the unknown. Because of this when we went to Isreal money became a problem, the imbalence became a problem. I was shown that the need to plan the world, stopped me from trusting in it. Everyone in my life has been following a plan and telling me I need money to live, everyone is telling me the colour of the water is green, but I am only seeing blue.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/dg-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/dg-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;something interesting&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/diary/a-world-at-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/diary/a-world-at-war/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;what&amp;rsquo;s Israel been like?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;while I&amp;rsquo;ve been hear for just under 3 months,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and am just beginning to understand the intensity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The truth is so complex and deeply woven into the systems and culture here. But it is not talked about, or recognized outwardly. The people seem to be facing an itch, and the itch is very real.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;when I first met dror I was scared to enter water so deep. It was scary at first to see into the problems he faced being Israeli, being jewish, and being the time. But this was just the beginning. Dror&amp;rsquo;s gift was his open heart to be able to welcome in all sides of the world. I realized later that this was a symptom of being exposed so many perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/divinely-guided/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/divinely-guided/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;in the most pure fashion, right straight and clear towards the people who align with me. They bring out my power, showing me it is huge. They bring up my fear of the size, they bring up the possibility of balance between the two.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I went my whole life being trapped in a world I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand and I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel I belonged to. Surrounded by a problem I could not grasp, by a world that was to powerful for me to handle. I hid from the size of the earth, i hid from my dream, I has to hide, I had to blend in, I had to get along.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/free-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/free-art/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;why is the art free&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the art is my gift to the world&#xA;I trust when I give it,&#xA;it will come back to me&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;when i started doing these portraits&#xA;people often gave donations anyway.&#xA;I trust the work will support me&#xA;and it has&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;creation as a statement of trust&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/idea-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/idea-book/</guid>
      <description>&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;title&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;theme&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;problem&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Soltuion&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Final Point&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;knowing less&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;knowing is a form of safety&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Safety in external structure&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;we are having an internal exteriepnce&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Creation is the act of making sense of an internal experience&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;The Internet Artist&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Algorithm puts expression into formulas&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Artists follow certain styles trends to get numerical appreciation&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Loose the need to make sense to other&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;the future belongs to those who take responsibility for their internal experience&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Responsibility&lt;br&gt;(video)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Your response ability&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Film story&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;what films taught me about reality&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;I began creating films about non sense&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;the non sense began to make sense to only me&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;my films began to reflect a story back to me about what I was going through inside&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Reflective reality&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;external world is a reflection of our internal experience&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;we rely on the external world to create our internal world. More we use external to make sense less internal makes sense&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;create to make sense of what we are going through inside&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;The world can become more and more revealing of our internal truth the more we see and treat it as a reflection of our inner world.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;The Creative Flip (video)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;sharing an internal world&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;notice the ways you turn to the external world to guide your experience&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;slowly practise ways of breaking free from acting through the experience of others&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;world begins to communicate with you, and you can deepen your experience here&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;sleepy pigeons&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;changing the form of a memory&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;if we are only focused on creating these monumental moments every moment is missing something.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;when we change the way we remember moments we change the vision for the future opens&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;our memory of the past is our vision for the future.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;to capture a memory&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Memory is a vision for the future&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;vision for the future becomes trapped in the boxes of other expectations&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Change the memory to open into a future&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;when we do not share for the approval of others,&lt;br&gt;we give ourself and others the permission to do the same&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;The quantum world&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;We have infinite potential&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;when we trap our perception into boxes of expectations, than we are conpressing our experince&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;don things without having a plan, practise intuition&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;what if their is a much deeper and fuller more richer experience waiting beyond what we assume we know&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;The collapse of time&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;what the quantum world has to do with our experience&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;When we plan and structure our time into boxes&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Our perception of time is in relationship to the quantum world.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Essence of time&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Time is patterns and patterns in cycles&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/letters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/letters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;my dearest dror, my big soft beautiful love,&#xA;I am writing you this today to move through some feelings I am having the trouble finding the words, maybe this will help me.&#xA;As I imagined wanting to write this I noticed a fear that came up, and saw a pattern in the relationship I had yet to see before. Our deep encouragement and love for each other, our foundation of building each other up, and making sure the other knows that they are the one for us, I noticed makes it challenging for me to bring up things that are not on this note.&#xA;Through many pages of writing this morning, I discovered that the need for my deepest communication is coming up now. A lot of it is in regards to learning how to express my boundaries, ask for what I need, and ultimately use my voice to its full potential. The world is telling that if I can find the words, if I can speak up for what I feel everything then every door that comes to be can be opened with grace.&#xA;On one layer this is showing up with Chen and the money, I am realizing I can have everything I want if I can ask for it. With this option open to me, I am able to see how much fear I have about asking for what I want and need.&#xA;On another layer this is happening with you, I feel fear about hurting you, and it&amp;rsquo;s creating a block in my heart and in my body. I cant escape a truth that I feel an attraction to this person. It snuck up on me in a weird way that I want to share with you in a fearlessly. When I first met him I was excited about being involved in this project, the more i&amp;rsquo;ve understood this project the more I saw how we are doing similar things in different ways. I can see how the universe is trying to help us bring the future alive for others. I have yet to meet someone who is doing it more than me, someone who is more obsessed with with creating a world that fosters the growth of the individual. I am experiencing a form of attraction I have never experienced before, and I want use our amazing communication skills to speak about our boundaries around me exploring it further.&#xA;Something I want to mention is how much love the thought of exploring this has brought into my life. For the connection I am experiencing with this person and very different from the one I am experiencing with you. The contrast is becoming clear to me that this is someone I would only want in my life in a very specific way, and it makes me see that he is not someone I would ever want to marry and combine together in life. His energy is far too outward than what I need. It makes me see even clearer that you are the one I will be having children with, you are the one I can spend the rest of my life with, and this person is here to teach me something very specific that will help me expand into the world.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Over the past few days I have felt a pain in my heart that I know you can feel. The pain is all the fear and guilt I have about having these feelings,&#xA;Im not sure what to do about this only that I wanted to speak about it with you on the phone when&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/letters/body-evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/letters/body-evolution/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;March 17th 1996 - the next galactic wave&#xA;Dear Ellias,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The body is hollow. Celestial fluid can play through the body, we do it all the time. Nothing is so very solid as we think. This is very fortunate, because the body is hollow the interior life forces are able to play through each layer of the body. They can bring in wave on wave of galactic forces - galaxy into life into matter, is the wave of time. But a body has remained somewhat static during the modern times, it has solidified into what seems like a very substantial, dense, heavy way of operating. Most of this energy in slowing down to almost inert levels, feels like it is not energy any longer but rather a thick consistency of &amp;ldquo;this is the way it always was and always will be.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/letters/profane-sacred-and-radical-death-edited/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/letters/profane-sacred-and-radical-death-edited/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;march 20. 1996&#xA;dear Ellias, there are traditions around drying that endure.&#xA;It was a scared passage before the scared withdrew from outer human awareness. *&#xA;When religion and symbolism trumped the outer literal awareness.*&#xA;Sacred death was the only way to go, we have never let go of the vision of sacred death, we simply reserve it for the few, the rare ones, and we envy them for still being able to unite with spirt as they die. &lt;em&gt;Sacred death is a myth and a memory, the little of what remains from the vision of a spirit world.&lt;/em&gt; But huge inroads have been made in modern times, in the human capacity to sustain the scared state of being, even at death. &lt;em&gt;As spirit weaves its way back into collective awareness we&amp;rsquo;re beginning to find a way to bridge the power of the individual with the power of the earth. In previous times the individual was at mercy to the earth, but as we&amp;rsquo;ve grown away from our reliance on time, as our basic needs are finally met, as we finally have the room to ask for more, the power of the individual can come home to the earth for the first time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/letters/surge-in-the-death-realms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/letters/surge-in-the-death-realms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;september 22 1999&#xA;the future surge in the death realms at the turning point in time&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;dear inner family,&#xA;the primacy of spirit connection is coming on alive amongst the living as a felt need, a desperate hunger in this changing crucial time. But people have burned their bridges to the wolds beyond, they have taught themselves not to go there for fear of deluding the self with idol fantasies, best to stay where we are and deal with what is right. So of us cast off our physical form among the dead, then we look back out there to the world of the living, the once born, and we here the cry, feel the need, get inside of the critical nature of what each one among the living is send out on subconscious frequency saying is there anybody here to help, is there any body I can believe in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/making-senses/finding-meaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/making-senses/finding-meaning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we want our life to mean something&#xA;we need a reason.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For a long time, the reason was survival.&#xA;Now we are here surviving,&#xA;doing much more than just surviving&#xA;and we still need a reason.&#xA;we can&amp;rsquo;t bare being helpless&#xA;for it doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense&#xA;to just be here and not have hope&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;hope waits around each corner,&#xA;hope has many streams of awareness inside&#xA;like a dice, hope has many sides,&#xA;something is bound to land&#xA;like a dice, the hope is cut by corners&#xA;and edges that slice it into a shape with sides&#xA;we loose the whole picture&#xA;the meaning is fragmented&#xA;cut by the need for numbers,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/making-senses/spirit-is-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/making-senses/spirit-is-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;science likes to recognize alot of the characteristics about the physical reality,&#xA;turns out the more we notice about how the physical reality work,&#xA;the more we can know how to make it work for us,&#xA;in this quest for more and more knowledge,&#xA;we forgot to look and seek deeper into the question of why?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;not why plants go through photosynthesis,&#xA;and all the deeper and deeper ways&#xA;that this creates and expresses whats going on around us,&#xA;but why does any of this happen,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/notes/the-way-we-communicate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/notes/the-way-we-communicate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;always changes&#xA;we are always expanding on our ability to communicate&#xA;we have compressed that ability&#xA;in this time and space,&#xA;as we have simaltainously exanding on our capability&#xA;to communiate, we have lost parts of our nature,&#xA;and are having to regain them&#xA;we are having to rember that communicate&#xA;is not depenading on numbers&#xA;because what we have done&#xA;is created the sellable characters to eachother,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/notes/transcribed-audio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/notes/transcribed-audio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i have always been interested in piegons&#xA;and it come because of a fear of them,&#xA;I was terrifled of them in university because they&#xA;were all over the city&#xA;they would come out of no where,&#xA;and they were huddled, togther,&#xA;and their reallly the only animal that has domesticated thmselves in a city&#xA;there these wld animals and they found a way t take advantage of humans&#xA;and i feel that sort of a part of me that I have been scared of but I feel&#xA;inisde like im a freakin piegon,&#xA;I feel like this crazy wid animal,&#xA;thats been placed in this modern world,&#xA;and trapped inside this city&#xA;and im just sort of like colecting the scraps of it&#xA;as I go along, blindly through the city&#xA;like the piegons&#xA;and thats what this account is,&#xA;is about that experince&#xA;that I am a sleepy peigon in this world&#xA;a dream I am collecting and making up from inside of me,&#xA;as i go along in this sort of city&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/notes/what-doesnt-make-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/notes/what-doesnt-make-sense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we don&amp;rsquo;t believe what doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense&#xA;what doesn&amp;rsquo;t add up in our mind,&#xA;anything with gaps we can&amp;rsquo;t believe in,&#xA;which is to say that we believe we&#xA;we can think up how everything works,&#xA;or/and we cant believe in anything thats unknown,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;don&amp;rsquo;t say stuff that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/plans/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/plans/list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;personally experienced world&#xA;made to make our own sense&#xA;time is pulled outside&#xA;films promote linear time,&#xA;when anything and every&#xA;thing is coming from inside&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;people are in their own world (film)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the process of people (film)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;paint to connect people (make)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;nothing lies outside itself (film)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;theory of relativity science film science and we are reflection to our world  to (make)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;creativity&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;we must not only create our worlds but the systems within them. Create systems around how you create.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;creativity is nothing but the refection it gives us.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the reflection has become refracted to find external validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;when we relate our creative experience  to numbers, we place a lens on the creativity that blocks the flow.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;we attempt t rationalize and know this world, thus preventing the possibility to flow through.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;creativity doesn&amp;rsquo;t want a place to go, or an identity, it wants to be, to be scene, to become something, so that it can act out and make sense of whats craving a voice inside.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;we must make sense of nonsense,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;we are always making sense of our world&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/plans/making-sense-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/plans/making-sense-course/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Synopsis:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many course available to teach many sides of life. We engage in learning so that we make more and more sense of our experience. This is a corse designed to teach you how to make sense of your world from the inside out, instead of looking to the world the outside to create your world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will explore our reliance on the external world to make sense to us and the way our perception of external time provokes us to make sense based on external systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/plans/mini-zines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/plans/mini-zines/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the impossible mountain&#xA;1.&#xA;a world that makes sense&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;technology land&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the lesson of the refection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/plans/themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/plans/themes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the memory of the past effects the vision of the future&lt;/strong&gt;- the way we remember events creates the pathway for us to form the future. Every future movement is made from a memory, everything we do comes from the memory of what we have done. When we deepen into the memory, then we can extend in to our future. By altering the way we envision the past we can remember how to be in the present, which is the future unfolding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/poems/a-love-for-isreal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/poems/a-love-for-isreal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;grows though hate,&#xA;grows through challenge,&#xA;grows through the people&#xA;who cannot understand this with their mind&#xA;grows as the branches of the darkness intertwine&#xA;my love grows with this land as my hearts set of fire,&#xA;my love grows through your love like the voice of a choir&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;love moves though me like you are the wind&#xA;ill move for you, Ill take it in,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/poems/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/poems/quotes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;a future where everyones famous&#xA;the only reason we admire fame is because it means someone came to earth, and did what nobody else could do. They did themselves and shared something we hadn&amp;rsquo;t yet experienced. This is not going to be a very big deal in the future, this is the goal we aim for, a world where everyone has permission to do themselves and the world supports their growth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/re-film-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/re-film-videos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the camera paradox - when your&amp;rsquo;e doing something cool, we are pulled to want to capture it, but when we capture it it never lives up to the actual moment. And if we do find a way to capture it that makes the moment seem as cool as it was, then there is often so much effort gone into capture the moment so that it looks cool, that the actual coolness of the moment is drained.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/script/a-very-unique-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/script/a-very-unique-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(shots of people doing things )&#xA;look around you,&#xA;each person is coming from an entirely different world,&#xA;no one of us has ever entered into each others worlds&#xA;we have been in the same world since the moment we came here,&#xA;no one has ever left,&#xA;we we go around pretending&#xA;we are living in the same world&#xA;notice your own world&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/script/note-book-typed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/script/note-book-typed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;place without rules&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;welcome to the creative sea&#xA;where everything you see&#xA;is an experience&#xA;a product of Einstein&amp;rsquo;s theory of relativity&#xA;everything is an experience relative to it self&#xA;what happens when we turn that fact into our creative reality&#xA;then everything becomes a personal experience&#xA;a perceptive event&#xA;everything is diluted into the senses&#xA;the bodily experience coming from many layers&#xA;coming through our senses, sight, hearing, touch, smell&#xA;coming through our perception of time,&#xA;the past, the future, the now and nothingness,&#xA;each person has been living under the spell&#xA;of their own creative trance&#xA;since the moment they were born&#xA;and since this moment is the only trackable reference&#xA;we have of where this experience began&#xA;and since we can see how everything is a perception,&#xA;we can see the only trackable difference we have&#xA;is the difference in the times we came from&#xA;the only thing that is real,&#xA;is birth and death,&#xA;everything else is made up from us,&#xA;the only thing we have no control over,&#xA;is the time we will die&#xA;and the time we are born&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/script/process-zine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/script/process-zine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the process zine is like a joke&#xA;in that i never know where its going on,&#xA;but it always has a punch line to give me,&#xA;a funny way that makes everything it did before&#xA;make sense&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;this project as a metaphor for trusting the creative process,&#xA;I wanted to see what was meant to learn from this process and the project&#xA;because the creative stream I would use to practise documenting and following this thing i trusted so deeply in,&#xA;the process,&#xA;and what happened was a deepening,&#xA;each layer would open me into a vaster understanding,&#xA;I began by eliminating any timeline I had on the project,&#xA;then I had to eliminate the need to share the process,&#xA;then it opened into many streams and sides&#xA;I began breaking down the natural process of creation through the stars&#xA;and creating my own language which taught me I had to&#xA;find another way of understanding this experience&#xA;and then I had to loose the need to understand it and wrap my head around it,&#xA;and now I am playing through multiple streams&#xA;different games on different layers of experiences&#xA;in things we call instagram accounts&#xA;and each one signifies a different layer of my conscious experience&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/script/reflections-and-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/script/reflections-and-numbers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the number we see on the screen&#xA;becomes a reflection of self&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;sometimes I think about how people&#xA;will judge my work based&#xA;on how many likes are follows I have,&#xA;when what i&amp;rsquo;ve found is&#xA;the less focus I have on likes and follows,&#xA;the better art gets produced&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/script/the-greatest-gift-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/script/the-greatest-gift-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the time we are give&#xA;the birthing of the unknown,&#xA;the understanding we receive from our experience&#xA;the world that becomes itself along the way,&#xA;promising us we are a part of something&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we have supplanted a plan&#xA;in place of unknown potential&#xA;and in the form of a clock,&#xA;trust in an undercurrent,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we pretend that time is a constant speed,&#xA;that it is something we have control of,&#xA;something we can make ours,&#xA;our time is our identity, our memory,&#xA;and tracking it is the way we&#xA;grip hold of this planet as it&#xA;apparently spins out of control&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/script/the-process-zine---a-tricky-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/script/the-process-zine---a-tricky-game/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the process zine is a tricky game I am playing with myself&#xA;as this world&#xA;it evolves using my reality as a test subject&#xA;to see if the truth of my one great knowing will arrive&#xA;if i use every second as a reason for it to exist,&#xA;if I can find the memory of why i am here in every moment&#xA;I am somewhere&#xA;one layer&#xA;always on the hunt&#xA;to discover how to trust myself more&#xA;how to find another reason that this reality is on my side&#xA;and believe that it has my best intentions&#xA;by believing this I am taken on a journey through every twist and turn&#xA;to bring me at rapid hurdling speed&#xA;towards a destiny that is mine to give&#xA;but it wont let down the performance,&#xA;the act of how to do so,&#xA;for it is not only paving the way,&#xA;it is leaving a trail&#xA;as evidence of creativity using itself to pull&#xA;itself from darkness&#xA;of the great pain and incredible power of how to do your destiny.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/script/time-is-a-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/script/time-is-a-story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;art is time&#xA;(close up shots of art in the home shot with camera, feeling is soft and mellow)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;close up shots of art, narrated&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;art is a reflection of time,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;time has a certain quality to it, and indescribable essence&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;it has a way it curves, it has a colour, a story, time has a meaning.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;art is a reflection, creation is a reflection&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;when we create with time, then our lives become a reflection of our work, our art&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;when we trust in the time that we already have what we need&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;then we do not work outside of time, attempting to achieve something we already are&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/shalagh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/shalagh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;hello,&#xA;my name is shalagh&#xA;its pronounced shay- la&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am using art to share a message about time. I am on a journey exchanging what I create for what i need in life. I offer free portraits in the street, and make money from donations. I paint walls in exchange for places to stay. I wshare that what we can trust in the journey when we follow it from inside.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/phone-sickness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/phone-sickness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The greatest danger of social media is the power it takes from actual reality. The way it strips existence of its imagined potential. Our imagination is our greatest power and we need it more than ever right now. Our imagination will pull us through this mess, but not like how we have imagined it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The future has let go of the identity that comes from screens. We understand that there is no substance to numbers and likes, and instead we choose participate in the online world because it can free us to go against the ingrained pattern in real life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/sharing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;share a vision inside&#xA;it helps to live into a vision for the future&#xA;by changing the memory of it&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;every move into the future,&#xA;every decision, every action, every desire&#xA;is a reflection of a memory,&#xA;the path we remember to take&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we are born story tellers,&#xA;we live into the story we tell ourselves,&#xA;what we create outside of ourself,&#xA;creates what we become within,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but rather the way our world is speaking to us&#xA;we create a different memory of the past,&#xA;and then we live into a different future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/social-media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;a streams for my dreams,&#xA;the behind the scenes&#xA;a means for the meaning&#xA;a screen for the feeling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the process zine is teaching me how to follow an internal process&#xA;rather than external time.&#xA;I am learning to learn through myself,&#xA;at this point it is letting all my creations free&#xA;letting the shadow expose itself&#xA;all of this feels like Ive just be practising&#xA;becoming. I am learning I don&amp;rsquo;t need to be liked or accepted,&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t need the external approval, its not what I came for&#xA;and its not what I want deep down,&#xA;i want to be free of time,&#xA;to give myself the room for creation to flow through me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/the-invention-of-screens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/the-invention-of-screens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the way screens become popular was through cartoons,&#xA;we created these characters and stories and fell in love with them&#xA;then slowly we started acting like them,&#xA;like the characters in the stories we watched,&#xA;and then slowly we became them,&#xA;characters on screens&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the screens show us what we create&#xA;reflects back into our experience&#xA;we have created a box for us to work for&#xA;a method and way for creativity to exists,&#xA;we need a character,&#xA;we need to play this game on the screen&#xA;to be cool enough to get attention,&#xA;from others,&#xA;be cool enough to get attention from yourself&#xA;to flip the reflection from the characters we became,&#xA;all the versions we took on&#xA;about the way it was suppose to look,&#xA;now we invent ourself out of that&#xA;by sharing and expressing&#xA;a world that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to anyone&#xA;but you,&#xA;we can remember how to take&#xA;responsibility for our life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/the-photo-struggle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/the-photo-struggle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;remember the feeling&#xA;when you try and capture a moment&#xA;and somethings missing&#xA;we want to capture the way it felt&#xA;the feeling can never be fully captured&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;yet we have this urge to capture the moments&#xA;to create a feeling&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the price of the moment has gone up&#xA;the right moment captured has a worth&#xA;a value, a future, a product,&#xA;we can make a living off of capturing moments&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/the-process-zine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/the-process-zine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;there has been something in side me baking,&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;its been life times in the making,&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;this meal that i&amp;rsquo;ve been craving&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;is finally ready for the saying&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the process has been a surface game i invented to play into my inner world, and see where it would take me. This journey took me far off screen and showed me why sharing it and trying to make life real online was taking away from this inner journey. This zine was a deep question inside, if technology could be used to express creativity how would it look? This has been this game to remember. It is not an instagram account, it is an inward timeline, a reflection of my inner experience, and now my inner experience is coming outside of me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/the-search-for-truth---technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/the-search-for-truth---technology/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;what technology is giving us is a direct reflection of self&#xA;we are given all the worlds we could have to reflect our truth,&#xA;in social media we are given a display of the worlds we think are true,&#xA;the worlds we are attracted to, the ones we believe in, the sides we love,&#xA;we follow&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;when technology began it was more a reflection of what technology could do,&#xA;everything was just a display of anything, because no one knew what the internet was for&#xA;slowly became a vessel to discover ourself through,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/social-media/the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/social-media/the-web/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the internet has a beautiful power,&#xA;to connect us&#xA;gives us endless possibility to interact with the people of our kin,&#xA;our our truth in a new form.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Until now our connection to each other has been hindered by race,&#xA;social group, and religon. Until now we have been connecting to people through a shared beleif systems and social structures from the world around us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The internet has a power to connect us with people of the same truth,&#xA;of the same inner beleif systems, of the same inner worlds,&#xA;but the power of the beast, requires us to learn to tell a new truth,&#xA;a new story to our brothers and sisters,&#xA;one that is of an inner truth,&#xA;a true truth.&#xA;Not of the one the world around us has projected upon us,&#xA;we are made to break the image this world has projected onto itself,&#xA;because it is hurting our souls,&#xA;we are at war,&#xA;fighting our brothers and sisters, about these made up systems,&#xA;about these external games, money, numbers, power, and religion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/star-time/making-less-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/star-time/making-less-sense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have developed a pattern of attempting to know the world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we love to plan our time, to make enough numbers, feed our tummies and make sure we have a home. That baseline pressure seeps into the way we make sense of the whole of life, creating the feeling that the more we know and gather from this experience the safer we are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a natural symptom at this point in time, for it was this outward pressure that created all the systems we form our lives around. All the ways we get our food and home and money and clothes and job and schools, all of it came from the search to know more about our world and ensure we are safe here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/star-time/planets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/star-time/planets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;each of the planets represents of time inside&#xA;each layer is happening at the same time&#xA;in a different way&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the darkness creates an illusion (pluto)&#xA;the illusion creates a reflection (neptune)&#xA;the reflection creates its experience in time (uranus)&#xA;the time gives us a vision to believe in (saturn)&#xA;the vision bring us into action (jupiter)&#xA;the actions brings us down to earth (mars)&#xA;the earth turns the action into feeling (moon)&#xA;the feeling senses a greater connection (venus)&#xA;the connection seeks expression (mercury)&#xA;the expression gives light to the dark (sun)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/star-time/the-greater-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/star-time/the-greater-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the solar system is not random,&#xA;everything is a part of a pattern,&#xA;everything we experience is part of a pattern&#xA;within another pattern&#xA;we a part of a greater system,&#xA;and it what we do with that awareness that matters,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we have to use this knowledge&#xA;that we have to actually apply it to our experience,&#xA;right now a lot of spiritually is surfacing,&#xA;but none of it has a grounds to make sense in&#xA;because of the greater system&#xA;we use to make sense of everything,&#xA;our collective perception of time,&#xA;does not provide the roots for it to grow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/star-time/the-moment-we-are-born/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/star-time/the-moment-we-are-born/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;our world stems from one moment,&#xA;and since that moment&#xA;we never left,&#xA;since the time of our birth&#xA;we have been living in our own entirely unique world,&#xA;in conjunction to everyone else&amp;rsquo;s entirely unique experience&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;if you really look at people&#xA;you will see something amazing is happening,&#xA;each person is in their entire own universe,&#xA;the one moment they have been in&#xA;since the day they were born,&#xA;the same moment&#xA;the one they they have created,&#xA;everything thing that they are,&#xA;stems from the moment they were created&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/aspects-generalizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/aspects-generalizations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;oppositions- direct sight into what is happening&#xA;returns- hold your hand bring you with me&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/astrology-is-not-a-personaility-trait/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/astrology-is-not-a-personaility-trait/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;it is a system of understanding our experience of time,&#xA;we have to see it as a whole,&#xA;to understand the process we are going through internally,&#xA;so we can live here internally,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the more we reinforce the external version of astrology,&#xA;the more we perpetuate taking our time out side of ourself,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;to understand astrology as a whole system&#xA;has the potential to change the world,&#xA;through each individual&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Why the book should be written?&#xA;Whats it about?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Along with rising interest in spirituality comes an increasing amount of scepticism and withdrawal because of the distance the subject matter carries from our reality. For many the subject of spirituality carries undertones that don&amp;rsquo;t align with the logical and rational world. There exists a gap between the world of spirit and very factual, time, and money driven world that we&amp;rsquo;re working with. As conflict increases within the current climate, so does the need for a solution that integrates the experience of spirit into the rational world. This book deals with the root question that started the discussion of spirit and the one we all face regardless of our beliefs, what happens when we die.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/degree-films/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/degree-films/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we are beyond any identity, sensing the epic, seeing the magnitude&#xA;Participating at full scale into the vastness beyond what anybody could imagine&#xA;Deeply aware I have a destiny here that is a part of the whole.&#xA;it is mapped out ahead of time, it demands a-lot of me and It never lets up, so neither do we.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am breaking free from the way it&amp;rsquo;s been done, opening a space and defying traditions.&#xA;The exception to every rule,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/houses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/houses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;first&#xA;we are brought into the centre of our most essential self where a core power remains as the world current fluctuates around. The senses and perception delicately stream the world through and creates a seemless relationship to the moment. The hope is to meet each moment a new so as not be caught in a previously experienced story. The power of the first house is in its openness and powerful centre that is alway open to give and receive new experiences. Everything is always changing, but whats essential stays. Through staying tuned in we become a vessel to sift through chaos and cling to what is true. We learn not overly consume our vitality and become in-tune with its constantly feeding rythmn. When we are really here we are accompanied by a pulse that will drift us naturally into each passing moment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/inside-degrees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/inside-degrees/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aries 1&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;Repairing and building a stone wall&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Our instinct is to use the materials of the world to create a boundaries for us to continue working in a straight forward manor&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The confrontation of the self with the material world.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Blocking out the complexities of the world.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The treasure we are protecting is ourselves, and we know how to move things out of our way.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We harness of internal strength in a straightforward motion, and love being in direct contact with the next piece needed to see the results of the wall.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We know what is needed inside, and do not need to justify the creation of the wall to the outside world.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The use of rocks of all shapes and sizes to find a way for them to fit together so that the self is protected.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aries 2 -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Stone steps descending into darkness&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/leo-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/leo-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we went from dreaming into a beautiful world, into dreaming into the world illusion, and becoming the star the world wanted from us, not the way we wanted the world to be. we are to caught into the celebrity fetish, we believe if we can shine individually.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;if you are true to yourself, there is no world that can mess you up there is no world that can stop you, thats how it really is.&#xA;the future is stying that your story, your myth, is about to be exploded into our story our myth.&#xA;to forget how to foregt and remember how to remember&#xA;were finding our earth legs, allowing us to be here as we truly are.&#xA;learn to descern past their own doubt, nothing will stop us but our own doubt. then you can see who is true, and apperance are realit and sensations are all we get&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/moon-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/moon-story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: Taking up where our instinctual drive moves us, testing and finding out how strong we are to extinguish any doubt we have in our capabilities. Discovering inner power.&#xA;Taurus: Living with our world our bubble, our familiar pattern, to change direction requires us to slowly integrate into unknown territory. Discovering unknown potential.&#xA;Gemini: Consistently and constantly weaving and integrating unknown and known worlds together through our inner known solid interior.&#xA;Cancer: Sees the world as a collective, works on the micro for the macro participating in where the collective is moving.&#xA;Leo: power of the heart comes to work for the world, inner potential becomes curious about where it comes from .&#xA;Virgo: We witness as many sides emerge from within, fine tuning our awareness to become clear about all the sides of the world.&#xA;Libra: Each space is its own world, we play into all the sides and external experience&amp;rsquo;s, until the internal world is full enough to be out guiding force. (taking on many sides and versions until the version inside is strong enough to guide us)&#xA;Scorpio: Diving deeply inward to self, taking up all the hidden shadows, to clear the karma&amp;gt;&#xA;Sag: Life becomes a mystery and we travel through it until the tension between being normal and being wild reveals our true nature.&#xA;Capricorn: Embodying full potential and high standards for self, until through sheer force of will we humble ourselves to see everything was a part of our own perfect becoming.&#xA;Aquarius: Perceiving the seen and unseen, the greater pattern, working for what we observe while keeping our inner world a mystery.&#xA;Pisces: Awake to the mysteries and tapping a creative power that transmutes darkness into rebirth!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/profane-sacred-and-radical-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/profane-sacred-and-radical-death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;march 20. 1996&#xA;dear Ellias, there are traditions around drying that endure.&#xA;It was a scared passage before the scared withdrew from outer human awareness. Sacred death was the only way to go, we have never let go of the vision of sacred death, we simply reserve it for the few, the rare ones, and we envy them for still being able to unite with spirt as they die. But huge inroads have been made in modern times, in the human capacity to sustain the scared state of being, even at death. This kind of passage has been supplanted fro the many by the inevitably of profane death, this is understanding because all of us are wrapped about in the tight net of the modern ideology, and the modern ideology states that there is no immortal soul and that each one when they die must face a vast abyss broadly speaking taking the profane death, as the only option is the universal agreement now.  A third kind of death also exists, it is the wave of the future I call it radical death, this is what im involved with completely, and the terms of it are to take the facaet of profane death that s vitally real, which is the loss of faith of something outside what we can directly experience for ourself (49:55) and combine his with the aspect of saced death that is most indispensable, which is to awaken to who we really are and what we belong to essentially in the act of dying. Radical death also brings into play a third and mighty factor that changes everything, let us first explore sacred death and profane death polarity in a fresh way, then we will be able to see how the radical death fuses these yet leaps beyond them all together.&#xA;Sacred death was always intended to be a deeply inward passage from one realm of god to another. If it was seen and felt to be keyed to assisting and mediating the passge from earth earth to heavene to take up the greater life beyond the physical. this much is obvious, profane death is now preceved as a mechanically driven empting of bodily life. The body seizes to work and we cant us it anymore, what ever beleifs or expectation we might consol our self with we shall be forced to give up the only life we know to take our chances on the dark unknown. It is a great loss, but it is also just how it is in this world, sad yet not all that important really, such is the basic picture. At the core of each of these models are many fascinating pictures, issues realizations, vision and experiences, most of which elude surface awarness all togther.&#xA;Let us now do complete justice to both of these realms of death. Sacred death was conceived in triumphant terms, the world was not all the real. the heavens we the greater destination, and the essence of our triumph was to be permitted to participate in a great adventure. We knew our bodies could not hold more than a fraction of our souls and our spirts, it was so clear to everybody that we dwelled beyond this life, so death was a nture counter part in every sense. Thats the beauty of sacred death was the longing in the heart satisfied, the deeper stirrings of our beings given their creative response by the angels, and divine forces. We were met by death transformed by it, profoundly transported to our greater destination. It was more miracle than anything else and given if most of us could not understand the whole of what this involved, might not remember to much about it, we knew it was a death designed for us, and we were ready for, even as we also saw a fullness in life before death, death was tied.&#xA;Profane death is primally a stark confrontation with ones one personal exisistance coming to a sudden abrupt hault, and being asked to find some way to more futher along by tapping our own inner resources, death is felt to be a terrible thing. Its only redemption lies in the one who is dying being able to discover a path which is real for them, and can be followed, only when courage and great struggle lead beyond, the brutal grave. The power in profane death is mustered within the stark will to come to ones self in the fires of burning up and losing ones life so decisively. It is an individual matter, each one is compelled to either loose everything, in the vapid nothingness, or to find a treasure that could never be assumed and is very hard earn whenever it is grasped.&#xA;Segments of humanity are draw back to scared death and other strictly go with the profane death, there are many who combine convictions in birth directions, we can see in the many current revolutions around death and near death each side and both together in a fascinating combination, most of those who seek a greater meaning in death are drawn back to the scared death of old, whether it is Tibetan Buddhism, alternative healing, the hostess movement or perhaps all of the traditional streams and convictions, the scared death calls us to rediscover its fruits. However it is all to easy to relax back into that faade of sacred death which we have evolved beyond and can retreat to in idealistic sentiment, but it is not really true. Profane death has taught us that each one must stay within their own immediate experience and be as vibrantly committed to their journey on its own terms as they can ever be. The clock cannot be turned back, it is so consoling to return to spirt roots in deeply uncertain times, but the truth is that profane death is in many ways an advance from the sacred death of old. One particular example must sufice; the side of sacred death which had to be put behind us at all costs is the perpetual dreaming into a mute surrender to the infinite power as living in the heavens as where we truly belong. This is a blasphemy on the earth experience, I will not go for it at all. Profane death lead us by the hand to recognize that we are very involved now with this earth and this body, and we cannot lightly leap forth into infinite brightness and just be glad to be done with mortal limitation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/sign-cycles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/sign-cycles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aries&lt;/strong&gt;- &lt;em&gt;self becomes empowered by itself&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All sides of self activated into central core current. We comes up against the shadow self. We are stuck on the truth of our existence, stark naked and honest. We begin Overflowing with the wonder of discovery. Becoming consumed by the upward direction of inner spirit. We bring spirit down by expressing it through the contact of senses on earth. Becoming divided by the rational earth and the direction of inner sprit. Life becomes a game of teasing in between the lines. The vision of the future must integrate the past. The rational side comes up against our need to make change. The higher self intervenes and becomes a central observer to our reality. We are faced with a continuous awakening to a higher presence. Forces ask us to strengthen by building up resistance from all in directed karma. Allowing us to become on our own path no matter what. We become plugged into the awareness of the unique self. Start cooking up our own raw intelligence from within. Senses become deeply in tune with the internal ripple of our experience. We come into presence within to be set free from our ego. Ego can no longer dictate our course and we move from a force within. The being is empty of identity and only moves from necessary action. All that is cultivated within begins to come true. We are taken by storm to let the journey of dreams unfold. Joy and freedom lead the way of self discovery. Our resources are stored within us waiting for the right time for them to be released. We gather remarkable inner strength and are stimulated by our destiny. Being able to do anything externally but cannot deny the shadow of experience. Greater forces intervene to accompany a destiny to make sure it will be fulfilled. These greater forces give light to the hidden parts of darkness. The image of who we are is dissolved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/star-activations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/star-activations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;bringing down the stars so that they become so alive within our own heart center. Not as an idea or concept but as something arises that we meet and comes to grips with as a living energetic frequency. We are amazing but not in the way the world has designed us to be.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;These 12 keys word activations, didn&amp;rsquo;t come up primary as words, although they were given words, they came up as impulses from 12 different star systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/the-zodiac-pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/the-zodiac-pattern/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;aries&#xA;self meets self&#xA;and learns world&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;taurus&#xA;self meets world&#xA;and learns destiny&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;gemini&#xA;self meets destiny&#xA;and learns presence&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;cancer&#xA;self meets presence&#xA;and learns heart&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;leo&#xA;self meets heart&#xA;and learns people&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;virgo&#xA;self meets people&#xA;and learns reflection&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;libra&#xA;self meets reflection&#xA;and learns darkness&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;scorpio&#xA;self meets darkness&#xA;and learn transformation&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;sag&#xA;self meets transformation&#xA;and learns truth&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;capricron&#xA;self meets truth&#xA;and learns vision&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/time-and-space---houses-and-pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/time-and-space---houses-and-pattern/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the signs represent how we experience the pattern&#xA;from a horizontal view,&#xA;as we move our head in a 360 circle,&#xA;we can see the various types of experiences&#xA;of layers of worlds that are happening around us,&#xA;we can notice how our continuous changes based on&#xA;what world we are located in&#xA;(space)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the houses represent how we experience the pattern&#xA;from a vertical view,&#xA;as we tilt our head,&#xA;we see the sun traveling through the sky,&#xA;we can notice how my experience and the&#xA;experience of whats around me&#xA;changes based on where the sun is in the sky.&#xA;(time)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/what-are-the-creatures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/what-are-the-creatures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the creatures are a language of symbolize&#xA;to describe the pattern of the zodiac&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the pattern of the zodiac is often understood&#xA;through the signs as as descriptions of characters,&#xA;and through the external experience and characteristics of each sign&#xA;We talk about the qualities of the Zodiac as the exists on the outside,&#xA;the pattern that the creatures symbolize is the internal experience,&#xA;and inner process of the signs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/you-cant-know-astrology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/you-cant-know-astrology/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;this situation is not something to be grasped&#xA;or used to define and predict this world in a known way,&#xA;the possibility is to transform the perception of the reality,&#xA;and stitch a deeper meaning into our incredibly personal experience&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;look around, everyone is living in their&#xA;own little universe.&#xA;Each one of us born from this planet,&#xA;and never left.&#xA;everyone is in their own world,&#xA;and the space that we came from,&#xA;is not a time,&#xA;it is an energetic expression&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/story/april.-13-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/story/april.-13-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;happy birthday Saturn. My chest felt so full this morning, i woke up to a feeling in my spine that had to get itself moving. It was the kind of anticipation I had waited my whole life for, and now it was coming. now I would make it into being. Now i would tell the story of my life.But it had to be slowly, to recokon with each  pice of its created form. I had been at work for years and now it was coming true. Not in one day, as a slow fade.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/story/life-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/story/life-story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;it started with the perception of time. It was clear to me as a little girl, something was going on behind the seems of all the planning adults were doing. There seemed to be another current creating this whole experince, and these adults seemed to be more in response to it, than they we creating with it. Much focus on time, getting on time, doing on time, having a good time. And yet something else seemed to persist stronger under all this planning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/story/origin-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/story/origin-story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;in university i was addicted to adhd pills&#xA;all my energy went into fulfilling the world outside of me,&#xA;when I found yoga I learned how to fulfill my inner world&#xA;I fell in love with the internal process of that was unfolding inside me&#xA;I became obsessed with astrology for it was the only thing I could find that gave credit to this internal process&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I studied it for years but could never understand where it came from&#xA;or why any of these charastictics came from&#xA;everything felt diluted and dumbed down into basic personality traits&#xA;then I discovered these 2 books&#xA;one went into each degree in the 360 degree pattern&#xA;the other went into each planet in all the signs and houses&#xA;they did not talk about the way astrology existed on the outside,&#xA;and instead focused on the inward experience&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/the-creation-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/the-creation-of-time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;it began with religion,&#xA;Organized religion turned our life in to the stage to work for something we receive when we leave this planet. The value of our experience was given over to god. Rules and formulas began to structure our behaviour on large scale. The church created a set of rules under the name of god, for us to behave. Our sense of self and who we were, came from our relationship to god - from a reference that has been defined for us. This taught the collective to rely on an external definition to create a sense of self. Religion had us working for the unknown.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/the-first-stroke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/the-first-stroke/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the first picture, the initial vision, the moment of impact, the channel of creativity, this is what is meant to be followed and trusted in.&#xA;In a world always focused on a creative projects final destination we give no credit to the initial vision. It gets revised, it can be played and and shifted on the ipad and photoshop. We never work with a mistake, we just erase and redo on the search for perfection. Taking the picture again and again until its perfect.&#xA;In this hunt, we have forget a nature of what creativity is, a moment of impact followed through, taken each moment to address what is there, to deal the real constraint of time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/the-game-of-time-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/the-game-of-time-story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;rule 1&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;enjoy the process&#xA;of learning about yourself&#xA;in everything you do&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;take everything you are going through&#xA;and see it as a lesson you are meant to learn&#xA;turn your lens into a curious study&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;exercise 1&#xA;the creative student of life&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;find a way to archaize your experience in different way&#xA;let the lessons that have created you, create you into being&#xA;create with the understanding to make sense of what your going through inside&#xA;practise creating without the lens of what anyone thinks,&#xA;and only to engage yourself in the process,&#xA;of transforming the way we make sense our our experience&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/the-game-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/the-game-of-time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;act 1&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;Notice the way your relationship to time shapes your experience.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notice the ways the value of time is perceived through the lens of numbers&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How the value of money shape a self, shapes the experience of the day.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How the feeling of a guarantee and sense of safety is something we can buy, determines the way we make sense of time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Notice how the numbers of likes, shapes the things you decide to notice in your time, the photos you decide to take. The time you decide to watch back later.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Notice how the frame of the numbers determines the time we give to what we do.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Notice how the reliance on the numbers leads to a society shaping everything into the box of a numerical value.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Notice how the feeling of prices shapes a self of self.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notice the system of times effect on self&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/the-infinity-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/the-infinity-effect/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Before infinity&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before this modern world, filled with millions of possibilities and infinite ways to make and use numbers, our sphere of focus was contained into the world around us, meeting our basic needs so we could survive. Our lives were simpler, we dealt with problems we don&amp;rsquo;t deal with today. We did not have the possibility to participate in infinite ways to do what we wanted with our time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/the-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/the-people/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the people have taught me I can trust this world&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am reminded every day that whatever I came to do,&#xA;is not for me, it is for the people.&#xA;I cannot do this alone, the people have been the #1 key to this all working out,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the people Ive met and had in my life have helped support me&#xA;and each have taught me that I can trust my world&#xA;Thank you for hosting me,&#xA;letting me work in my own time,&#xA;giving me your spaces,&#xA;bringing me into your family,&#xA;cooking me food.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/the-process/the-numbers-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/the-process/the-numbers-effect/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the effect of numbers is a result&#xA;of our experience of time.&#xA;numbers have created multiple streams in this shared reality&#xA;that cause us to rely on validate, and make sense of our time through their systems&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This piece explores the rise in popularity and reliance on numbers, and our slowly built dependancy on this created system. We will see how the use of numbers came to ripple so deeply into the collective psych and the way we form, comprehend and understand reality. Numbers are not just used to plan our time, and give us a salary, they carry an energy of certainty, of calculation, and of validating our self.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/the-process/what-the-process-has-taught-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/the-process/what-the-process-has-taught-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;to do things before I know why.&#xA;To act upon a feeling, a vision, and imagination inside of me, and trust it has somewhere to take me.&#xA;To closely track me experience inside to see where to go,&#xA;and where ever I go somehow ends up making sense why I went there.&#xA;The more time I travel from this direction the more sense everything make to me,&#xA;to me, literally, to me. The world starts to make sense to me instead of me trying to make sense of it.&#xA;I become the listener the observer and my experince becomes the conversation.&#xA;Everywhere I go it has something to teach me, to show me about hw it is connecting to my inner experinces. Nothng is forgein all is welcome, when you trust the process.&#xA;It is much more than just casually witnessing you reality go by,&#xA;to trust in the process is to actually do something with it, and then see whee it has to take you,&#xA;this is not a paassive exsistance, it is a persuasive one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/time/science-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/time/science-time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;everything is happening inside itself&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;all the science and all the unknown answers its searching for&#xA;are all saying the same thing&#xA;because we are thinking about it in one lens&#xA;but as soon as we get down to the particle layer&#xA;the lens itself switches,&#xA;the observer creates the reality of the particle,&#xA;as soon as we enter the quantum worlds,&#xA;the laws change&#xA;we cannot measure things in the same way&#xA;the same things don&amp;rsquo;t apply&#xA;quantum entanglement, string theory,&#xA;quantum field theory,&#xA;all say the the same thing,&#xA;that the time we feel is not real like we imagine,&#xA;this does not mean we cant imagine it&#xA;we just have to imagine beyond the reality that we created,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/time/suffering-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/time/suffering-of-time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we rate our suffering on the basis of external experience,&#xA;peoples life conditions, money situation, and trama,&#xA;however there is suffering in having everything&#xA;a kind of suffer we don&amp;rsquo;t know how to talk bad out because&#xA;its so recent in human history that such large sums&#xA;of people had have their needs mets and live in worlds&#xA;where are  their needs are met for them&#xA;this suburban situation is having its first time in history&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/time/the-atlaain-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/time/the-atlaain-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the atlantion system used the signs from the tranditonal&#xA;zoaidc but sees them from a different oder,&#xA;this perse&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/time/the-sacrifice-of-knowing-the-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/time/the-sacrifice-of-knowing-the-time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we use time&#xA;to define time,&#xA;an idea we created&#xA;has now created itself into us&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;everything we do&#xA;is in reference to time&#xA;our conscious experience is in a calculative dance&#xA;with the time thats moving around us&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we want to do the most with it,&#xA;we want to make some prof of it,&#xA;we want cash in our hands to know&#xA;our time has value&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and the numbers give us the prof of the value of the time,&#xA;they give us meaning, they give us food on our table.&#xA;through numbers we survive&#xA;so it makes sense that we give them a lot of credit&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/time/the-value-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/time/the-value-of-time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Time is art&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and like art,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;its value goes up with time,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The further we get away from the origin of creation,&#xA;The more deeply we value its existence&#xA;When we create with time,&#xA;allowing it to take us over,&#xA;The value of our time deepens,&#xA;Seconds become more meaningful,&#xA;And the essence of the day is imbued,&#xA;with the building an inner kingdom,&#xA;Let the frequency dig deeper,&#xA;The waves of experience craved further into the walls,&#xA;We let creation through us&#xA;We let it take over,&#xA;We become the thread,&#xA;Conciseness rides its way through the reflections&#xA;And threaded through so that the time&#xA;Unfolds, it grows and stacks in circles,&#xA;And cycles, patterns, meaning and senses&#xA;Are engaged and tapped into an activate&#xA;Process&#xA;Time is art&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/time/the-worth-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/time/the-worth-of-time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Underneath the sea of infinite scrolling is the desire to give our time away and make it worth something to someone else. We share stuff and cool moments and all sides of our life and what we are saying underneath the surface is I want to take your time, I want to get your attention. We are taking something from each other with this need to entertain, we are feeding our friends, followers, and the world we love, with more and more information. Maybe this information is helpful, but is it helpful that we provoke others to rely on these screens to receive what we need? and what are we taking from their experience by providing this entertainment?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/time/time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/time/time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;time is how we make sense of our world.&#xA;time creates the structures, the systems, and the systems within the systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;time makes all the worlds go round and grow.&#xA;time is growing at different rates within different worlds.&#xA;time is growing at different rates within the worlds inside us&#xA;time is happening at multiple layers at once&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we are comprehending different layers of time at the same time&#xA;we can listen to different layers of time inside us&#xA;different time layers carry different visions&#xA;and different memories,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/time/we-cant-acknowledge-something-so-obvious/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/time/we-cant-acknowledge-something-so-obvious/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we will go insane&#xA;before we let it make sense&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;it would collapse the&#xA;mental frame work of everything&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;all this mental frame work&#xA;is supporting an idea,&#xA;and all it takes is for that idea&#xA;to mean something completely different&lt;br&gt;&#xA;for all the frame work to collapse&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;time is an invention&#xA;that creates the experience&#xA;that this world is happening&#xA;outside of ourself&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;time provokes our perception&#xA;to seek for numerical validation&#xA;to make sense of itself&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/transferred/the-power-of-the-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/transferred/the-power-of-the-truth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;to tell the truth is hard, we all want a nice story, we all want to be insightful and innocent, powerful and truthful. We cannot escape the truth, it will haunt us until we can express it. It will hang out on our shoulder warping and twisting this world around it. If we do not speak our truth then everything will reflect back through the lies we told. We have to opportunity to free ourself, to see through all of it, but it takes a lot of courage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/transferred/to-capture-a-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/transferred/to-capture-a-memory/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;we pull too the screen to re-live our experience.&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;To become ignited by a memory,&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;we yearn into the moment to remember the feeling&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;and seek to recreate it again.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we peel back the experience of a memory it quickly revels itself as our vision for the future. Each step we take, each move we make is based on the memory of where we are going, of what we are doing. There is no present moment, there is only a memory of the past, reflected as a vision for the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/transferred/why-believe-in-other-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/transferred/why-believe-in-other-lives/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;why believe in other life times..?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;not all like times are meant to shine&#xA;some are meant to stay inside&#xA;the ones that shine spent a long time&#xA;inside before they decide to come alive&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the thing that stops us from appreciating our differences,&#xA;the trap that gets us into envy those who came to shine,&#xA;is the illusion of time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we think that we&amp;rsquo;re suppose to do something shiny&#xA;we give credit to the external evidence&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/untitled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/untitled/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/website/30-second-portraits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/website/30-second-portraits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;why is the art free?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;*the art i is an expression of a trust&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i trust my hand on the paper,&#xA;I trust the people I meet&#xA;i trust in the value of what I create&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;when I began offer the portraits for free&#xA;I was able to draw much more people&#xA;and I learned people often instinctually decided to donate&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want to give you the option to define the value of the work&#xA;I want to give you the option to have a piece of art for free&#xA;I want to trust what i create will support me if I give it to the world&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/aries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/aries/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Libra Earth: Submerged in the collective undercurrent and feeling like there is no room for any new individual. This energy is hard to take, and means we meet our connections with an undercurrent infused with anger and a drive to remove all closeness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Aries Sun: We are infused with a spark and direction forward that blows away the clusters of everything one cannot meet. The gates are open for a new consciousness to witness its aliveness. Taking this star all the way is to set this a fresh pace to allow others to be fully and unapologetically themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/aspects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/aspects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sun and Moon&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the dance of these bodies illuminates the space between earth and the cosmos. The sun gives the energy, and the moon brings it down into earthy rhythm giving on a playground to come into self and follow their destiny.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sun conjunct Moon: In tune with instincts and able to take the steps forward to participate readily and willingly towards ones own becoming. awaiting the space where full embodiment can stream through fluidly. Propelled by destiny, yet unable to move into this space until the instinctual knowing arises. No pretending, the patience of intuition, knowing where it belongs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/jupiter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/jupiter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: Quick sharp discovery response to surroundings, attempting to divide the world into right and wrong. A dualistic perspective, charged and determined to come out on top being right. The internal drama is hot, and he plays out his reason why hard. As much as he reveals as the good guy, will be as much as is obstructed to reveal a contradicting perspective.Learning not to let the dialect consume him to leave space to see in between the lines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/mars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: Aware of our concerns and directing them forward to widen the space. Learning to integrate the concerns of the world with the concerns of self. When tuned in he can use this energy to widen the social sphere for everyone, but when he feels like his ideas are not respected by the world, he turns to dominance and aggression. Here it is clear he is his own worst enemy, and is learning to respect his own ideas. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t need approval to be himself, but he does need to approve himself, to be approved by others.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/neptune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/neptune/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: 1860s A serge to discover emerges and the sense that the old structures are becoming powerless pushes a break through to a new living future. A need to reform and advocate for change, passionately streams through as a beacon of destiny. Each one on their own journey, trampling over each other in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taurus: 1870-80s Earth begins to surrender to the forces of human will. Amplified growth in industry ignites new found external potential. Underneath a magical time of rebirth is occurring where we begin to see the earth a living light, alive with forces beyond what had ever been possibly imagined.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/pluto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/pluto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: 1820-1850 A world centred around personal life presents the possibility for new potential. To grasp that the human experience encompasses many dimensions and possibilities had not yet been played upon. Intense drive towards forward motion and future currents. Seeing open possibility in a hard headed world, when everything is alive on the surface.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taurus: 1850s-1860s the earth comes alive inside the human being and we cannot explain the vastness we are tapping. Technology advancements heighten the importance of remaining natural and returning to the earth. Drawn into territory where we may feel alone, yet in the hands of angels. Those who have tapped this earth sensibility lay their eggs under the surface for growth down the line.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/saturn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/saturn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: A striking force becoming vibrantly present with a piercing desire to move anything that gets in the way of the truth unfolding. Sharp attention to what is meant to move, and whatever is causing a disturbance will be removed uncompromisingly. We are reckoning with defeat from karmic experiences that have devastated a spirit. We are powered beyond our pity with an intense focus on the present. This is the journey where the mental focus is tested, tried and strengthened to move past any doubts of a past swamped in depths.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/uranus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/uranus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: 1920s and 30s&amp;rsquo; We are stung with an entirely new impulse to take action as the divide between the world becomes too hot to handle. Overtaken by an impulse to get on with future and weaving into everyday. Working to take our passion from its wild frenzy into a focus that can reorient itself to a new life force.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taurus: Mid 1930s The earth is alive with new design and potential visions for the future. We participate with the  electric state and impulse for the future. The vision of a new earth is an obvious and inevitable outcome and no one can deny it is being birthed a new way of being.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/venus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/venus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: We sees ourself in the world and seek to discover who we are though the other. Constantly discoveringthe feeling the other creates in our own heart. The playground of relationships continues to expand as long as the other can stand its ground and give her the space to dance around, if the other is just recitable as she, she will recognize her loneliness. That she is seeking a piece of herself in the other. She will join into a relationship with herself, to discover the missing piece she was seeking in the other.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing-done/screen-less-worlds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing-done/screen-less-worlds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;imagine a world without this screen&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;in this world,&#xA;anything you want to create&#xA;you must find it in reality,&#xA;you must engage in the steps forward&#xA;to put what you imagination into action,&#xA;we must work into the vision of&#xA;what we want to see happen&#xA;we have to make sense of the problem,&#xA;to make sense from non sense&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we have to create how we sense,&#xA;to give life to the unknown,&#xA;and along the way,&#xA;the conversation between our senses&#xA;stitches together the known and unknown,&#xA;and the process becomes a dance,&#xA;of revealing itself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing-done/the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing-done/the-internet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the internet is where we come to know things&#xA;to be a valid human&#xA;to get numbers and confirm we are accepted&#xA;we use technology factually, realistically&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the internet is something we take seriously&#xA;as a reflection of our identity&#xA;its not a place to be something you&amp;rsquo;r&amp;rsquo;e not&#xA;we share to put our best foot forward&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we like and follow each other&#xA;to reinforce that we are having a&#xA;valid human experience here&#xA;and the closer you can follow a formula,&#xA;the more it appears you are connected to humanity&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/can-i-tell-you-a-joke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/can-i-tell-you-a-joke/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;sure, you say&#xA;you begin listening,&#xA;not seriously and kinda curiously&#xA;because you know what your hearing is going to change&#xA;because its a joke&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the punch line comes&#xA;but the punch line was not the joke&#xA;it was the perceived reality&#xA;prior to the punch line&#xA;that is the joke&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the world is a joke and&#xA;everything you experience is&#xA;has the potential to reveal&lt;br&gt;&#xA;an ironic outcome&#xA;if you don&amp;rsquo;t hold it seriously&#xA;and listen curiously&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/collective-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/collective-identity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the conflict is not with the identity it is the way we form our identity. How we can form it together around a main idea. We must central our forces around a main idea within the identity of ourself. There are o many conflicts within conflicts. One side beleives in beleiving in something else outside of itself, the right side wants a leader, it wats someone to tell them what to do.the left side wants themslefs, they want to spread. they cannot unite in the same way as the right. It is not just a conflict between 2 groups of people it is the conflict behnd what we are fighting for. While the left takes up its own path of self identiy, and then forms its belief system around, its journey, passion, hearts path, to choose a cause that benifits the whole. The left will fight for the future. While the right is fighting to maintain, to stay the same, to protect their identity, which is tied into the pattern they have always known. There is no searching for expansion of knowledge, of insight, their is a guard up. They want the land, they want the known, they dont want chaos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/everything-is-perception/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/everything-is-perception/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;but where are the facts&#xA;what is the evidence that can prove this.&#xA;fact comes from science,&#xA;science cannot fathom the existence of both&#xA;fact and perception&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we are both getting to know&#xA;our world,&#xA;and getting to know&#xA;what it means&#xA;truth is both fact and perception&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;both are based on each other,&#xA;never separate&#xA;co existing in a dance&#xA;to get us to grasp and&#xA;sense into our world&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/fun-thats-been-created-for-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/fun-thats-been-created-for-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we lost the ability to have fun&#xA;when did you forget to play, when did you become ashamed, and when did the ability to dream fade away,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/he-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/he-said/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;he said you notice the patterns,&#xA;and then you identify with it,&#xA;that is not how smart works&#xA;i thought thats how i&amp;rsquo;ve learnt to love,&#xA;from the insides out,&#xA;this is spirituality,&#xA;in a world of facts, I don&amp;rsquo;t care how you see it,&#xA;the shift is not from the outside in,&#xA;you must learn youre youre own,&#xA;person,&#xA;own experience,&#xA;made to unfold,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i see him doing math,&#xA;amI jealous I didn&amp;rsquo;t train my brain that way,&#xA;or am i grateful i cant work with numbers the same,&#xA;i said dror,&#xA;I love your brain,&#xA;but i really wanna know, does it make you insane.&#xA;is playing sane, a part of the pain,&#xA;or do you really like thinking that way,&#xA;because I lost need,&#xA;the ability to see,&#xA;how the world adds up logically,&#xA;I left it behind, and I cant look back,&#xA;because something about being an artist&#xA;is so much more interesting.&#xA;am i sorry for the way i feel,&#xA;dont let me steal the dignity ,&#xA;youve collected from thiscollectve frequency,&#xA;is it to real for you,&#xA;the me i cant not be,&#xA;or can you prentend,&#xA;and pay this game with me,&#xA;I dont want to make sense,&#xA;I dont want the proff&#xA;for I built this house without a roof&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/imagine-your-imagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/imagine-your-imagination/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;remember its power&#xA;when we were young&#xA;and could get wrapped up for hours&#xA;in our invented mind,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and somewhere along the lines&#xA;we had to give over this power&#xA;to what was real,&#xA;what was proof,&#xA;what was good,&#xA;what was cool&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we lost the ability to&#xA;invent this place into our home&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;creativity is not an art practise&#xA;it is not something we make time for&#xA;it is never separate from any moment&#xA;its always happening&#xA;with each moment we make&#xA;more and more sense of our world&#xA;we are imagining into our reality&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/israel-giving-up-the-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/israel-giving-up-the-image/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i always had a feeling I would have to get over what people thought of me, and I wondered how I would ever get there. I got so good at being great for others, how could I let this image free.&#xA;Israel is spitting truth in my face in the most beautiful tragic and mesmoring ways, i am forgetting whats its like to care what other think of me. My old life in Canada feels like a dream I cant remember how it felt to be there. Only the images reply in my mind about the person I tried so hard to be.&#xA;I never felt at home in Canada, I felt like an alien. Someone way far removed from its context.&#xA;Here in Israel I feel I have met my people again. These people are faced with the deep complex truth of reality, each one of them has to deal with the dark shadows of life in there own way. No one can pretend here. I came from pretend land, where the only problems we must face are domestic. I came from a safe space, I came from protection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/knowing-unknowness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/knowing-unknowness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we don&amp;rsquo;t get to know things before they happen,&#xA;because it is the process of knowing them&#xA;where we come alive.&#xA;It is the decisions and options that present themselves,&#xA;that reveal the known direction.&#xA;So when we land at the known,&#xA;we can trust that it was the unknown that got us there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the relationship we build,&#xA;and the unknown direction becomes more known.&#xA;As long as we can always know&#xA;that we will know where to go,&#xA;then we can exsist with peace here on earth,&#xA;in the unknown.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/multiple-layers-of-conciseness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/multiple-layers-of-conciseness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;experience is always crossing a threshold beyond what exists&#xA;as it creates in one way,&#xA;it simultaneously creates for another&#xA;in another side of consciousness&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we talk about all these states of conciseness,&#xA;like we move in and out of them,&#xA;but we don&amp;rsquo;t move into an unconscious state,&#xA;the unconscious state is always happening&#xA;at the same time&#xA;as the conscious one&#xA;we cant shut any layer off,&#xA;multiple states are always happening at once,&#xA;and each one is has its own unique relationship to each other&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/the-slice-of-pie-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/the-slice-of-pie-game/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we are a part of a game. &amp;ldquo;god creation or whatever has invented for us a place and time and space for the whole to come home to. It was created invented a system that would play out all sides of experience,to bring the experience closer to soul. Each individual was a part of the whole coming home, and each one was responsible for addressing sides of the pattern, so that the whole dish can be cooked, and eventually distilled back to its core.It was the journey, the process of this alchemy , we are meant to come and experience. In each life time, following a strand of continuously, constantly weaving and forming like a dna strand. We must respect each-other for their part in the pattern.We must remember for ourself, to remember for those around.We have the opportunity to create tremendous waves through out ability to follow the natural path of creation.To understand what is compromising the system as a part of understanding of self.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/this-world-is-coming-from-within/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/this-world-is-coming-from-within/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;science validates our experience&#xA;with the proof from the external reality&#xA;by attempting to add it up and make it all make sense&#xA;but everything on this planet is an internal experience&#xA;everything we experience is our individual perception.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we can agree upon things,&#xA;there can be a correct answer&#xA;but even the answer&#xA;meant something different to everyone&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s the last thing we would acknowledge&#xA;in a connection&#xA;but the first thing that motivates us to connect&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/what-makes-us-different/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/what-makes-us-different/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the time and space we came from&#xA;we pretend that there is the prescription for all of time&#xA;religion would give every individual  the same prescription&lt;br&gt;&#xA;for all time and space.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we believe their is a sort of&#xA;formula for doing human&#xA;and we check with the external reality&#xA;on how to behave&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we celebrate and acknowledge our differences&#xA;in appearance, and beliefs,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(religion)&#xA;the idea that where we came from&#xA;and our age does not determine our differences&#xA;but&#xA;and instead makes up a portion of our differences,&#xA;and rather physical appearance gets more credit&#xA;as a differences than age&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/zine/expression-and-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/zine/expression-and-language/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we come from different places,&#xA;we&amp;rsquo;ve created different ways to express these places in words,&#xA;these words are a reflection of the time and space,&#xA;where we will, how we live, what we live with,&#xA;we&amp;rsquo;ve invented similar things in different places,&#xA;and have different words,&#xA;the words are the formula for expression of life,&#xA;the formula we&amp;rsquo;ve created for us to communicate,&#xA;yet even through different languages, the expression&#xA;of communication remains the same,&#xA;when we say different words, we use the same emphasis&#xA;on words when we&amp;rsquo;re angry, or loving, or happy,&#xA;we understand, and know inherently the language of&#xA;expression. Of subtle features,&#xA;micro expressions,&#xA;and art.&#xA;There is a difference between the formula (words) and the expression (communication),&#xA;and both exist and are pervasively intertwined,&#xA;yet the formula express&amp;rsquo;s a definition,&#xA;and the expression doesn&amp;rsquo;t need it, it exists on its own ,&#xA;yet this concept foundational to own we think,&#xA;seeps down into other facets of our experience,&#xA;where we attempt to control and define or&#xA;and formulate how we express ourself.&#xA;Its like we cant separate creativity from our mind,&#xA;we can imagine yet that there is an imagined,&#xA;and imagining reality, happening both at once.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/zine/game-of-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/zine/game-of-earth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we cannot pretend to know where someone is coming from&#xA;we cannot pretend that we come from a world that we know&#xA;we are each coming from our own entirely unique world&#xA;and to pretend that we know whats going on&#xA;is to play the game of known reality&#xA;which is not the game of earth&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we did not come to earth to know anything&#xA;we came to explore, to be the thing we always were&#xA;a part of this planet, a piece of a system&#xA;the natural spinning and rising cycles as earth&#xA;we are not on a planet, we are a planet&#xA;and when we remember this,&#xA;we don&amp;rsquo;t form our memory around who we are&#xA;and all the things that came together towards what we see&#xA;we form our reality around what we are experiencing&#xA;in this moment through our senses&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/zine/saying-something-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/zine/saying-something-simple/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;something simple that requires, dumbing down our brains,&#xA;shutting off the knowing valve,&#xA;and the gathering evidence to formulate a problem,&#xA;towards become a part of the problem, its one slight shift into&#xA;into a world that changes the perspective on every world you move through.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The point is to change the relationship between the self and their world,&#xA;we are born with a feeling of connectedness and then slowly become separated,&#xA;as humanity pulls us through puberty, the humiliating stage of adopting an identity,&#xA;and we see our world as a place to build our identity,&#xA;everything in the world becomes a product of who we are,&#xA;everything is a personal reflection of our identity in contrast to the world&#xA;we have a comparative lens towards what is us, and what is not.&#xA;we have preferences, schedules, and goals to formulate our identity into existence&#xA;the calendar calculates&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/zine/social-acceptability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/zine/social-acceptability/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;she got brains and good looks&#xA;so she fell social acceptability&#xA;and got high on surface appearance&#xA;addiction forced her to see&#xA;the deepest parts of herself,&#xA;to make sense of the nonsense&#xA;the journey was carefully crafted&#xA;and the job was hers,&#xA;she suffered for the earth&#xA;to learn to remember&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/zine/value-of-time-inside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/zine/value-of-time-inside/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I believe we have to give more value to the time unfolding inside of us&#xA;it appears our world has found a numerical system for naming and identifying time&#xA;into money and numbers, and this system in no way gives credit to the&#xA;mystery seeking to unfold from within.&#xA;we must begin the shift in our world&#xA;through the perception of time,&#xA;once we can recognize that we&#xA;are ourself a product of creation,&#xA;their are no facts, and we are a living perception,&#xA;then we can begin to shift our values from&#xA;relying on and cultivating external truth,&#xA;to embodying nonsense.&#xA;We can loosen the need to reinforce plans&#xA;and make sure everything is right,&#xA;when we can see that nothing was right or wrong,&#xA;that it was all happening as a part of the creative process.&#xA;When we can understand this and apply this to our lives&#xA;then our we become less driven towards controlling the external processes,&#xA;and begin to listen to the subtitles of the internal processes which allow us&#xA;to sync with the existing flow rather than&#xA;calculate it and consume it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/zine/what-im-trying-to-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/zine/what-im-trying-to-say/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we give the external world a lot of credit for how we feel.&#xA;We make it seem like how we feel comes from the external experience.&#xA;But no matter what experience we&amp;rsquo;re feeling, it remains inside.&#xA;We can&amp;rsquo;t create anything in the external world, without creating it first inside of us.&#xA;Everything is happening inside of us, not one person living the same world.&#xA;and yet the external world does everything it can to attempt find&#xA;ways of validating and knowing&#xA;ourself from an outer known perspective.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
