<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Plans on My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/plans/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Plans on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/plans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/plans/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/plans/list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;personally experienced world&#xA;made to make our own sense&#xA;time is pulled outside&#xA;films promote linear time,&#xA;when anything and every&#xA;thing is coming from inside&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;people are in their own world (film)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the process of people (film)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;paint to connect people (make)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;nothing lies outside itself (film)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;theory of relativity science film science and we are reflection to our world  to (make)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;creativity&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;we must not only create our worlds but the systems within them. Create systems around how you create.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;creativity is nothing but the refection it gives us.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the reflection has become refracted to find external validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;when we relate our creative experience  to numbers, we place a lens on the creativity that blocks the flow.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;we attempt t rationalize and know this world, thus preventing the possibility to flow through.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;creativity doesn&amp;rsquo;t want a place to go, or an identity, it wants to be, to be scene, to become something, so that it can act out and make sense of whats craving a voice inside.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;we must make sense of nonsense,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;we are always making sense of our world&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/plans/making-sense-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/plans/making-sense-course/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Synopsis:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many course available to teach many sides of life. We engage in learning so that we make more and more sense of our experience. This is a corse designed to teach you how to make sense of your world from the inside out, instead of looking to the world the outside to create your world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will explore our reliance on the external world to make sense to us and the way our perception of external time provokes us to make sense based on external systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/plans/mini-zines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/plans/mini-zines/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the impossible mountain&#xA;1.&#xA;a world that makes sense&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;technology land&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the lesson of the refection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/plans/themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/plans/themes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the memory of the past effects the vision of the future&lt;/strong&gt;- the way we remember events creates the pathway for us to form the future. Every future movement is made from a memory, everything we do comes from the memory of what we have done. When we deepen into the memory, then we can extend in to our future. By altering the way we envision the past we can remember how to be in the present, which is the future unfolding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
