<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stars on My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/stars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stars on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/stars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/aspects-generalizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/aspects-generalizations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;oppositions- direct sight into what is happening&#xA;returns- hold your hand bring you with me&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/astrology-is-not-a-personaility-trait/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/astrology-is-not-a-personaility-trait/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;it is a system of understanding our experience of time,&#xA;we have to see it as a whole,&#xA;to understand the process we are going through internally,&#xA;so we can live here internally,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the more we reinforce the external version of astrology,&#xA;the more we perpetuate taking our time out side of ourself,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;to understand astrology as a whole system&#xA;has the potential to change the world,&#xA;through each individual&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Why the book should be written?&#xA;Whats it about?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Along with rising interest in spirituality comes an increasing amount of scepticism and withdrawal because of the distance the subject matter carries from our reality. For many the subject of spirituality carries undertones that don&amp;rsquo;t align with the logical and rational world. There exists a gap between the world of spirit and very factual, time, and money driven world that we&amp;rsquo;re working with. As conflict increases within the current climate, so does the need for a solution that integrates the experience of spirit into the rational world. This book deals with the root question that started the discussion of spirit and the one we all face regardless of our beliefs, what happens when we die.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/degree-films/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/degree-films/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we are beyond any identity, sensing the epic, seeing the magnitude&#xA;Participating at full scale into the vastness beyond what anybody could imagine&#xA;Deeply aware I have a destiny here that is a part of the whole.&#xA;it is mapped out ahead of time, it demands a-lot of me and It never lets up, so neither do we.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am breaking free from the way it&amp;rsquo;s been done, opening a space and defying traditions.&#xA;The exception to every rule,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/houses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/houses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;first&#xA;we are brought into the centre of our most essential self where a core power remains as the world current fluctuates around. The senses and perception delicately stream the world through and creates a seemless relationship to the moment. The hope is to meet each moment a new so as not be caught in a previously experienced story. The power of the first house is in its openness and powerful centre that is alway open to give and receive new experiences. Everything is always changing, but whats essential stays. Through staying tuned in we become a vessel to sift through chaos and cling to what is true. We learn not overly consume our vitality and become in-tune with its constantly feeding rythmn. When we are really here we are accompanied by a pulse that will drift us naturally into each passing moment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/inside-degrees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/inside-degrees/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aries 1&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;Repairing and building a stone wall&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Our instinct is to use the materials of the world to create a boundaries for us to continue working in a straight forward manor&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The confrontation of the self with the material world. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Blocking out the complexities of the world. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The treasure we are protecting is ourselves, and we know how to move things out of our way. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We harness of internal strength in a straightforward motion, and love being in direct contact with the next piece needed to see the results of the wall. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We know what is needed inside, and do not need to justify the creation of the wall to the outside world. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The use of rocks of all shapes and sizes to find a way for them to fit together so that the self is protected. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aries 2 -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Stone steps descending into darkness&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/leo-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/leo-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we went from dreaming into a beautiful world, into dreaming into the world illusion, and becoming the star the world wanted from us, not the way we wanted the world to be. we are to caught into the celebrity fetish, we believe if we can shine individually.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;if you are true to yourself, there is no world that can mess you up there is no world that can stop you, thats how it really is.&#xA;the future is stying that your story, your myth, is about to be exploded into our story our myth.&#xA;to forget how to foregt and remember how to remember&#xA;were finding our earth legs, allowing us to be here as we truly are.&#xA;learn to descern past their own doubt, nothing will stop us but our own doubt. then you can see who is true, and apperance are realit and sensations are all we get&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/moon-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/moon-story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: Taking up where our instinctual drive moves us, testing and finding out how strong we are to extinguish any doubt we have in our capabilities. Discovering inner power.&#xA;Taurus: Living with our world our bubble, our familiar pattern, to change direction requires us to slowly integrate into unknown territory. Discovering unknown potential.&#xA;Gemini: Consistently and constantly weaving and integrating unknown and known worlds together through our inner known solid interior.&#xA;Cancer: Sees the world as a collective, works on the micro for the macro participating in where the collective is moving.&#xA;Leo: power of the heart comes to work for the world, inner potential becomes curious about where it comes from .&#xA;Virgo: We witness as many sides emerge from within, fine tuning our awareness to become clear about all the sides of the world.&#xA;Libra: Each space is its own world, we play into all the sides and external experience&amp;rsquo;s, until the internal world is full enough to be out guiding force. (taking on many sides and versions until the version inside is strong enough to guide us)&#xA;Scorpio: Diving deeply inward to self, taking up all the hidden shadows, to clear the karma&amp;gt;&#xA;Sag: Life becomes a mystery and we travel through it until the tension between being normal and being wild reveals our true nature.&#xA;Capricorn: Embodying full potential and high standards for self, until through sheer force of will we humble ourselves to see everything was a part of our own perfect becoming.&#xA;Aquarius: Perceiving the seen and unseen, the greater pattern, working for what we observe while keeping our inner world a mystery.&#xA;Pisces: Awake to the mysteries and tapping a creative power that transmutes darkness into rebirth!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/profane-sacred-and-radical-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/profane-sacred-and-radical-death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;march 20. 1996&#xA;dear Ellias, there are traditions around drying that endure.&#xA;It was a scared passage before the scared withdrew from outer human awareness. Sacred death was the only way to go, we have never let go of the vision of sacred death, we simply reserve it for the few, the rare ones, and we envy them for still being able to unite with spirt as they die. But huge inroads have been made in modern times, in the human capacity to sustain the scared state of being, even at death. This kind of passage has been supplanted fro the many by the inevitably of profane death, this is understanding because all of us are wrapped about in the tight net of the modern ideology, and the modern ideology states that there is no immortal soul and that each one when they die must face a vast abyss broadly speaking taking the profane death, as the only option is the universal agreement now.  A third kind of death also exists, it is the wave of the future I call it radical death, this is what im involved with completely, and the terms of it are to take the facaet of profane death that s vitally real, which is the loss of faith of something outside what we can directly experience for ourself (49:55) and combine his with the aspect of saced death that is most indispensable, which is to awaken to who we really are and what we belong to essentially in the act of dying. Radical death also brings into play a third and mighty factor that changes everything, let us first explore sacred death and profane death polarity in a fresh way, then we will be able to see how the radical death fuses these yet leaps beyond them all together.&#xA;Sacred death was always intended to be a deeply inward passage from one realm of god to another. If it was seen and felt to be keyed to assisting and mediating the passge from earth earth to heavene to take up the greater life beyond the physical. this much is obvious, profane death is now preceved as a mechanically driven empting of bodily life. The body seizes to work and we cant us it anymore, what ever beleifs or expectation we might consol our self with we shall be forced to give up the only life we know to take our chances on the dark unknown. It is a great loss, but it is also just how it is in this world, sad yet not all that important really, such is the basic picture. At the core of each of these models are many fascinating pictures, issues realizations, vision and experiences, most of which elude surface awarness all togther.&#xA;Let us now do complete justice to both of these realms of death. Sacred death was conceived in triumphant terms, the world was not all the real. the heavens we the greater destination, and the essence of our triumph was to be permitted to participate in a great adventure. We knew our bodies could not hold more than a fraction of our souls and our spirts, it was so clear to everybody that we dwelled beyond this life, so death was a nture counter part in every sense. Thats the beauty of sacred death was the longing in the heart satisfied, the deeper stirrings of our beings given their creative response by the angels, and divine forces. We were met by death transformed by it, profoundly transported to our greater destination. It was more miracle than anything else and given if most of us could not understand the whole of what this involved, might not remember to much about it, we knew it was a death designed for us, and we were ready for, even as we also saw a fullness in life before death, death was tied.&#xA;Profane death is primally a stark confrontation with ones one personal exisistance coming to a sudden abrupt hault, and being asked to find some way to more futher along by tapping our own inner resources, death is felt to be a terrible thing. Its only redemption lies in the one who is dying being able to discover a path which is real for them, and can be followed, only when courage and great struggle lead beyond, the brutal grave. The power in profane death is mustered within the stark will to come to ones self in the fires of burning up and losing ones life so decisively. It is an individual matter, each one is compelled to either loose everything, in the vapid nothingness, or to find a treasure that could never be assumed and is very hard earn whenever it is grasped.&#xA;Segments of humanity are draw back to scared death and other strictly go with the profane death, there are many who combine convictions in birth directions, we can see in the many current revolutions around death and near death each side and both together in a fascinating combination, most of those who seek a greater meaning in death are drawn back to the scared death of old, whether it is Tibetan Buddhism, alternative healing, the hostess movement or perhaps all of the traditional streams and convictions, the scared death calls us to rediscover its fruits. However it is all to easy to relax back into that façade of sacred death which we have evolved beyond and can retreat to in idealistic sentiment, but it is not really true. Profane death has taught us that each one must stay within their own immediate experience and be as vibrantly committed to their journey on its own terms as they can ever be. The clock cannot be turned back, it is so consoling to return to spirt roots in deeply uncertain times, but the truth is that profane death is in many ways an advance from the sacred death of old. One particular example must sufice; the side of sacred death which had to be put behind us at all costs is the perpetual dreaming into a mute surrender to the infinite power as living in the heavens as where we truly belong. This is a blasphemy on the earth experience, I will not go for it at all. Profane death lead us by the hand to recognize that we are very involved now with this earth and this body, and we cannot lightly leap forth into infinite brightness and just be glad to be done with mortal limitation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/sign-cycles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/sign-cycles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aries&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;self becomes empowered by itself&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All sides of self activated into central core current. We comes up against the shadow self. We are stuck on the truth of our existence, stark naked and honest. We begin Overflowing with the wonder of discovery. Becoming consumed by the upward direction of inner spirit. We bring spirit down by expressing it through the contact of senses on earth. Becoming divided by the rational earth and the direction of inner sprit. Life becomes a game of teasing in between the lines. The vision of the future must integrate the past. The rational side comes up against our need to make change. The higher self intervenes and becomes a central observer to our reality. We are faced with a continuous awakening to a higher presence. Forces ask us to strengthen by building up resistance from all in directed karma. Allowing us to become on our own path no matter what. We become plugged into the awareness of the unique self. Start cooking up our own raw intelligence from within. Senses become deeply in tune with the internal ripple of our experience. We come into presence within to be set free from our ego. Ego can no longer dictate our course and we move from a force within. The being is empty of identity and only moves from necessary action. All that is cultivated within begins to come true. We are taken by storm to let the journey of dreams unfold. Joy and freedom lead the way of self discovery. Our resources are stored within us waiting for the right time for them to be released. We gather remarkable inner strength and are stimulated by our destiny. Being able to do anything externally but cannot deny the shadow of experience. Greater forces intervene to accompany a destiny to make sure it will be fulfilled. These greater forces give light to the hidden parts of darkness. The image of who we are is dissolved. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/star-activations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/star-activations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;bringing down the stars so that they become so alive within our own heart center. Not as an idea or concept but as something arises that we meet and comes to grips with as a living energetic frequency. We are amazing but not in the way the world has designed us to be.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;These 12 keys word activations, didn&amp;rsquo;t come up primary as words, although they were given words, they came up as impulses from 12 different star systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/the-zodiac-pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/the-zodiac-pattern/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;aries&#xA;self meets self&#xA;and learns world&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;taurus&#xA;self meets world&#xA;and learns destiny&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;gemini&#xA;self meets destiny&#xA;and learns presence&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;cancer&#xA;self meets presence&#xA;and learns heart&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;leo&#xA;self meets heart&#xA;and learns people&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;virgo&#xA;self meets people&#xA;and learns reflection&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;libra&#xA;self meets reflection&#xA;and learns darkness&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;scorpio&#xA;self meets darkness&#xA;and learn transformation&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;sag&#xA;self meets transformation&#xA;and learns truth&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;capricron&#xA;self meets truth&#xA;and learns vision&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/time-and-space---houses-and-pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/time-and-space---houses-and-pattern/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the signs represent how we experience the pattern&#xA;from a horizontal view,&#xA;as we move our head in a 360 circle,&#xA;we can see the various types of experiences&#xA;of layers of worlds that are happening around us,&#xA;we can notice how our continuous changes based on&#xA;what world we are located in&#xA;(space)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the houses represent how we experience the pattern&#xA;from a vertical view,&#xA;as we tilt our head,&#xA;we see the sun traveling through the sky,&#xA;we can notice how my experience and the&#xA;experience of whats around me&#xA;changes based on where the sun is in the sky.&#xA;(time)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/what-are-the-creatures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/what-are-the-creatures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the creatures are a language of symbolize&#xA;to describe the pattern of the zodiac&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the pattern of the zodiac is often understood&#xA;through the signs as as descriptions of characters,&#xA;and through the external experience and characteristics of each sign&#xA;We talk about the qualities of the Zodiac as the exists on the outside,&#xA;the pattern that the creatures symbolize is the internal experience,&#xA;and inner process of the signs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/stars/you-cant-know-astrology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/stars/you-cant-know-astrology/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;this situation is not something to be grasped&#xA;or used to define and predict this world in a known way,&#xA;the possibility is to transform the perception of the reality,&#xA;and stitch a deeper meaning into our incredibly personal experience&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;look around, everyone is living in their&#xA;own little universe.&#xA;Each one of us born from this planet,&#xA;and never left.&#xA;everyone is in their own world,&#xA;and the space that we came from,&#xA;is not a time,&#xA;it is an energetic expression&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
