<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wheels on My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/wheel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wheels on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/wheel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/aries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/aries/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Libra Earth: Submerged in the collective undercurrent and feeling like there is no room for any new individual. This energy is hard to take, and means we meet our connections with an undercurrent infused with anger and a drive to remove all closeness. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Aries Sun: We are infused with a spark and direction forward that blows away the clusters of everything one cannot meet. The gates are open for a new consciousness to witness its aliveness. Taking this star all the way is to set this a fresh pace to allow others to be fully and unapologetically themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/aspects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/aspects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sun and Moon&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the dance of these bodies illuminates the space between earth and the cosmos. The sun gives the energy, and the moon brings it down into earthy rhythm giving on a playground to come into self and follow their destiny.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sun conjunct Moon: In tune with instincts and able to take the steps forward to participate readily and willingly towards ones own becoming. awaiting the space where full embodiment can stream through fluidly. Propelled by destiny, yet unable to move into this space until the instinctual knowing arises. No pretending, the patience of intuition, knowing where it belongs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/jupiter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/jupiter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: Quick sharp discovery response to surroundings, attempting to divide the world into right and wrong. A dualistic perspective, charged and determined to come out on top being right. The internal drama is hot, and he plays out his reason why hard. As much as he reveals as the good guy, will be as much as is obstructed to reveal a contradicting perspective. Learning not to let the dialect consume him to leave space to see in between the lines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/mars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: Aware of our concerns and directing them forward to widen the space. Learning to integrate the concerns of the world with the concerns of self. When tuned in he can use this energy to widen the social sphere for everyone, but when he feels like his ideas are not respected by the world, he turns to dominance and aggression. Here it is clear he is his own worst enemy, and is learning to respect his own ideas. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t need approval to be himself, but he does need to approve himself, to be approved by others. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/neptune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/neptune/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: 1860’s A serge to discover emerges and the sense that the old structures are becoming powerless pushes a break through to a new living future. A need to reform and advocate for change, passionately streams through as a beacon of destiny. Each one on their own journey, trampling over each other in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taurus: 1870-80’s Earth begins to surrender to the forces of human will. Amplified growth in industry ignites new found external potential. Underneath a magical time of rebirth is occurring where we begin to see the earth a living light, alive with forces beyond what had ever been possibly imagined.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/pluto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/pluto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: 1820-1850 A world centred around personal life presents the possibility for new potential. To grasp that the human experience encompasses many dimensions and possibilities had not yet been played upon. Intense drive towards forward motion and future currents. Seeing open possibility in a hard headed world, when everything is alive on the surface.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taurus: 1850s-1860s the earth comes alive inside the human being and we cannot explain the vastness we are tapping. Technology advancements heighten the importance of remaining natural and returning to the earth. Drawn into territory where we may feel alone, yet in the hands of angels. Those who have tapped this earth sensibility lay their eggs under the surface for growth down the line.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/saturn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/saturn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: A striking force becoming vibrantly present with a piercing desire to move anything that gets in the way of the truth unfolding. Sharp attention to what is meant to move, and whatever is causing a disturbance will be removed uncompromisingly. We are reckoning with defeat from karmic experiences that have devastated a spirit. We are powered beyond our pity with an intense focus on the present. This is the journey where the mental focus is tested, tried and strengthened to move past any doubts of a past swamped in depths.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/uranus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/uranus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: 1920s and 30s&amp;rsquo; We are stung with an entirely new impulse to take action as the divide between the world becomes too hot to handle. Overtaken by an impulse to get on with future and weaving into everyday. Working to take our passion from its wild frenzy into a focus that can reorient itself to a new life force.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taurus: Mid 1930s The earth is alive with new design and potential visions for the future. We participate with the  electric state and impulse for the future. The vision of a new earth is an obvious and inevitable outcome and no one can deny it is being birthed a new way of being.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/wheel/venus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/wheel/venus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aries: We sees ourself in the world and seek to discover who we are though the other. Constantly discovering the feeling the other creates in our own heart. The playground of relationships continues to expand as long as the other can stand its ground and give her the space to dance around, if the other is just recitable as she, she will recognize her loneliness. That she is seeking a piece of herself in the other. She will join into a relationship with herself, to discover the missing piece she was seeking in the other. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
