<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arts on My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arts on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/art/slowly-remembering-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/art/slowly-remembering-why/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i don&amp;rsquo;t make art to make art&#xA;its an experiment&#xA;to see if I could trust in time&#xA;to see if I could let my inner world be,&#xA;what would it have to show me&#xA;to see what the creative process had to say when I trusted in it,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;what i learned was, this process did not want to be planned,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;when I surrendered I was given something&#xA;beyond what I could have expected&#xA;the process wants to remain unknown&#xA;when I didn&amp;rsquo;t confine the experience to money or numbers or time,&#xA;It always led me to create a different exchange&#xA;that allowed something much stronger to flow through&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/art/the-tragic-story-of-money-and-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/art/the-tragic-story-of-money-and-art/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I has a classic experience where I saw a wall that looked like it could use a mural and talked to the owner. At first he&amp;rsquo;s super stoked about the idea, we talk about a vision, I show him my previous work, we get the excited about the idea of the art, and then begin to talk logistics. Getting the paint? sure he can pay for it! Then i mention gently, that ive done alot of work for free, and I just cant do that anymore - I should get paid for the work. He agrees, but the entire demeanour of the conversation changes. Now things are serious, now comes the determining factor, will there even be this beautiful imaginary project if the numbers don&amp;rsquo;t make sense. There comes a pause, and my partner and him start talking in Hebrew, I see the man back down saying , loh loh, the translation is no, no in english. The idea is cancelled, a number was mentioned beyond what made sense to the owner and the moments over.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
