<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Star Times on My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/star-time/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Star Times on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/star-time/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/star-time/making-less-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/star-time/making-less-sense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have developed a pattern of attempting to know the world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we love to plan our time, to make enough numbers, feed our tummies and make sure we have a home. That baseline pressure seeps into the way we make sense of the whole of life, creating the feeling that the more we know and gather from this experience the safer we are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a natural symptom at this point in time, for it was this outward pressure that created all the systems we form our lives around. All the ways we get our food and home and money and clothes and job and schools, all of it came from the search to know more about our world and ensure we are safe here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/star-time/planets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/star-time/planets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;each of the planets represents of time inside&#xA;each layer is happening at the same time&#xA;in a different way&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the darkness creates an illusion (pluto)&#xA;the illusion creates a reflection (neptune)&#xA;the reflection creates its experience in time (uranus)&#xA;the time gives us a vision to believe in (saturn)&#xA;the vision bring us into action (jupiter)&#xA;the actions brings us down to earth (mars)&#xA;the earth turns the action into feeling (moon)&#xA;the feeling senses a greater connection (venus)&#xA;the connection seeks expression (mercury)&#xA;the expression gives light to the dark (sun)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/star-time/the-greater-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/star-time/the-greater-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the solar system is not random,&#xA;everything is a part of a pattern,&#xA;everything we experience is part of a pattern&#xA;within another pattern&#xA;we a part of a greater system,&#xA;and it what we do with that awareness that matters,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we have to use this knowledge&#xA;that we have to actually apply it to our experience,&#xA;right now a lot of spiritually is surfacing,&#xA;but none of it has a grounds to make sense in&#xA;because of the greater system&#xA;we use to make sense of everything,&#xA;our collective perception of time,&#xA;does not provide the roots for it to grow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/star-time/the-moment-we-are-born/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/star-time/the-moment-we-are-born/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;our world stems from one moment,&#xA;and since that moment&#xA;we never left,&#xA;since the time of our birth&#xA;we have been living in our own entirely unique world,&#xA;in conjunction to everyone else&amp;rsquo;s entirely unique experience&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;if you really look at people&#xA;you will see something amazing is happening,&#xA;each person is in their entire own universe,&#xA;the one moment they have been in&#xA;since the day they were born,&#xA;the same moment&#xA;the one they they have created,&#xA;everything thing that they are,&#xA;stems from the moment they were created&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
