<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories on My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/story/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stories on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/story/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/story/april.-13-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/story/april.-13-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;happy birthday Saturn. My chest felt so full this morning, i woke up to a feeling in my spine that had to get itself moving. It was the kind of anticipation I had waited my whole life for, and now it was coming. now I would make it into being. Now i would tell the story of my life.But it had to be slowly, to recokon with each  pice of its created form. I had been at work for years and now it was coming true. Not in one day, as a slow fade.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/story/life-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/story/life-story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;it started with the perception of time. It was clear to me as a little girl, something was going on behind the seems of all the planning adults were doing. There seemed to be another current creating this whole experince, and these adults seemed to be more in response to it, than they we creating with it. Much focus on time, getting on time, doing on time, having a good time. And yet something else seemed to persist stronger under all this planning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/story/origin-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/story/origin-story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;in university i was addicted to adhd pills&#xA;all my energy went into fulfilling the world outside of me,&#xA;when I found yoga I learned how to fulfill my inner world&#xA;I fell in love with the internal process of that was unfolding inside me&#xA;I became obsessed with astrology for it was the only thing I could find that gave credit to this internal process&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I studied it for years but could never understand where it came from&#xA;or why any of these charastictics came from&#xA;everything felt diluted and dumbed down into basic personality traits&#xA;then I discovered these 2 books&#xA;one went into each degree in the 360 degree pattern&#xA;the other went into each planet in all the signs and houses&#xA;they did not talk about the way astrology existed on the outside,&#xA;and instead focused on the inward experience&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
