<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Processes on My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/the-process/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Processes on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/the-process/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/the-process/the-numbers-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/the-process/the-numbers-effect/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the effect of numbers is a result&#xA;of our experience of time.&#xA;numbers have created multiple streams in this shared reality&#xA;that cause us to rely on validate, and make sense of our time through their systems&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This piece explores the rise in popularity and reliance on numbers, and our slowly built dependancy on this created system. We will see how the use of numbers came to ripple so deeply into the collective psych and the way we form, comprehend and understand reality. Numbers are not just used to plan our time, and give us a salary, they carry an energy of certainty, of calculation, and of validating our self.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/the-process/what-the-process-has-taught-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/the-process/what-the-process-has-taught-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;to do things before I know why.&#xA;To act upon a feeling, a vision, and imagination inside of me, and trust it has somewhere to take me.&#xA;To closely track me experience inside to see where to go,&#xA;and where ever I go somehow ends up making sense why I went there.&#xA;The more time I travel from this direction the more sense everything make to me,&#xA;to me, literally, to me. The world starts to make sense to me instead of me trying to make sense of it.&#xA;I become the listener the observer and my experince becomes the conversation.&#xA;Everywhere I go it has something to teach me, to show me about hw it is connecting to my inner experinces. Nothng is forgein all is welcome, when you trust the process.&#xA;It is much more than just casually witnessing you reality go by,&#xA;to trust in the process is to actually do something with it, and then see whee it has to take you,&#xA;this is not a paassive exsistance, it is a persuasive one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
