<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writings on My Obsidian Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writings on My Obsidian Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/can-i-tell-you-a-joke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/can-i-tell-you-a-joke/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;sure, you say&#xA;you begin listening,&#xA;not seriously and kinda curiously&#xA;because you know what your hearing is going to change&#xA;because its a joke&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the punch line comes&#xA;but the punch line was not the joke&#xA;it was the perceived reality&#xA;prior to the punch line&#xA;that is the joke&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the world is a joke and&#xA;everything you experience is&#xA;has the potential to reveal&lt;br&gt;&#xA;an ironic outcome&#xA;if you don&amp;rsquo;t hold it seriously&#xA;and listen curiously&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/collective-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/collective-identity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the conflict is not with the identity it is the way we form our identity. How we can form it together around a main idea. We must central our forces around a main idea within the identity of ourself. There are o many conflicts within conflicts. One side beleives in beleiving in something else outside of itself, the right side wants a leader, it wats someone to tell them what to do.the left side wants themslefs, they want to spread. they cannot unite in the same way as the right. It is not just a conflict between 2 groups of people it is the conflict behnd what we are fighting for. While the left takes up its own path of self identiy, and then forms its belief system around, its journey, passion, hearts path, to choose a cause that benifits the whole. The left will fight for the future. While the right is fighting to maintain, to stay the same, to protect their identity, which is tied into the pattern they have always known. There is no searching for expansion of knowledge, of insight, their is a guard up. They want the land, they want the known, they dont want chaos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/everything-is-perception/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/everything-is-perception/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;but where are the facts&#xA;what is the evidence that can prove this.&#xA;fact comes from science,&#xA;science cannot fathom the existence of both&#xA;fact and perception&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we are both getting to know&#xA;our world,&#xA;and getting to know&#xA;what it means&#xA;truth is both fact and perception&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;both are based on each other,&#xA;never separate&#xA;co existing in a dance&#xA;to get us to grasp and&#xA;sense into our world&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/fun-thats-been-created-for-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/fun-thats-been-created-for-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we lost the ability to have fun&#xA;when did you forget to play, when did you become ashamed, and when did the ability to dream fade away,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/he-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/he-said/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;he said you notice the patterns,&#xA;and then you identify with it,&#xA;that is not how smart works&#xA;i thought thats how i&amp;rsquo;ve learnt to love,&#xA;from the insides out,&#xA;this is spirituality,&#xA;in a world of facts, I don&amp;rsquo;t care how you see it,&#xA;the shift is not from the outside in,&#xA;you must learn youre youre own,&#xA;person,&#xA;own experience,&#xA;made to unfold,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i see him doing math,&#xA;amI jealous I didn&amp;rsquo;t train my brain that way,&#xA;or am i grateful i cant work with numbers the same,&#xA;i said dror,&#xA;I love your brain,&#xA;but i really wanna know, does it make you insane.&#xA;is playing sane, a part of the pain,&#xA;or do you really like thinking that way,&#xA;because I lost need,&#xA;the ability to see,&#xA;how the world adds up logically,&#xA;I left it behind, and I cant look back,&#xA;because something about being an artist&#xA;is so much more interesting.&#xA;am i sorry for the way i feel,&#xA;dont let me steal the dignity ,&#xA;youve collected from thiscollectve frequency,&#xA;is it to real for you,&#xA;the me i cant not be,&#xA;or can you prentend,&#xA;and pay this game with me,&#xA;I dont want to make sense,&#xA;I dont want the proff&#xA;for I built this house without a roof&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/imagine-your-imagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/imagine-your-imagination/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;remember its power&#xA;when we were young&#xA;and could get wrapped up for hours&#xA;in our invented mind,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and somewhere along the lines&#xA;we had to give over this power&#xA;to what was real,&#xA;what was proof,&#xA;what was good,&#xA;what was cool&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we lost the ability to&#xA;invent this place into our home&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;creativity is not an art practise&#xA;it is not something we make time for&#xA;it is never separate from any moment&#xA;its always happening&#xA;with each moment we make&#xA;more and more sense of our world&#xA;we are imagining into our reality&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/israel-giving-up-the-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/israel-giving-up-the-image/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i always had a feeling I would have to get over what people thought of me, and I wondered how I would ever get there. I got so good at being great for others, how could I let this image free.&#xA;Israel is spitting truth in my face in the most beautiful tragic and mesmoring ways, i am forgetting whats its like to care what other think of me. My old life in Canada feels like a dream I cant remember how it felt to be there. Only the images reply in my mind about the person I tried so hard to be.&#xA;I never felt at home in Canada, I felt like an alien. Someone way far removed from its context.&#xA;Here in Israel I feel I have met my people again. These people are faced with the deep complex truth of reality, each one of them has to deal with the dark shadows of life in there own way. No one can pretend here. I came from pretend land, where the only problems we must face are domestic. I came from a safe space, I came from protection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/knowing-unknowness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/knowing-unknowness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we don&amp;rsquo;t get to know things before they happen,&#xA;because it is the process of knowing them&#xA;where we come alive.&#xA;It is the decisions and options that present themselves,&#xA;that reveal the known direction.&#xA;So when we land at the known,&#xA;we can trust that it was the unknown that got us there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the relationship we build,&#xA;and the unknown direction becomes more known.&#xA;As long as we can always know&#xA;that we will know where to go,&#xA;then we can exsist with peace here on earth,&#xA;in the unknown.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/multiple-layers-of-conciseness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/multiple-layers-of-conciseness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;experience is always crossing a threshold beyond what exists&#xA;as it creates in one way,&#xA;it simultaneously creates for another&#xA;in another side of consciousness&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we talk about all these states of conciseness,&#xA;like we move in and out of them,&#xA;but we don&amp;rsquo;t move into an unconscious state,&#xA;the unconscious state is always happening&#xA;at the same time&#xA;as the conscious one&#xA;we cant shut any layer off,&#xA;multiple states are always happening at once,&#xA;and each one is has its own unique relationship to each other&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/the-slice-of-pie-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/the-slice-of-pie-game/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we are a part of a game. &amp;ldquo;god creation or whatever has invented for us a place and time and space for the whole to come home to. It was created invented a system that would play out all sides of experience,to bring the experience closer to soul. Each individual was a part of the whole coming home, and each one was responsible for addressing sides of the pattern, so that the whole dish can be cooked, and eventually distilled back to its core.It was the journey, the process of this alchemy , we are meant to come and experience. In each life time, following a strand of continuously, constantly weaving and forming like a dna strand. We must respect each-other for their part in the pattern.We must remember for ourself, to remember for those around.We have the opportunity to create tremendous waves through out ability to follow the natural path of creation.To understand what is compromising the system as a part of understanding of self.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/this-world-is-coming-from-within/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/this-world-is-coming-from-within/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;science validates our experience&#xA;with the proof from the external reality&#xA;by attempting to add it up and make it all make sense&#xA;but everything on this planet is an internal experience&#xA;everything we experience is our individual perception.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we can agree upon things,&#xA;there can be a correct answer&#xA;but even the answer&#xA;meant something different to everyone&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s the last thing we would acknowledge&#xA;in a connection&#xA;but the first thing that motivates us to connect&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/writing/what-makes-us-different/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/writing/what-makes-us-different/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the time and space we came from&#xA;we pretend that there is the prescription for all of time&#xA;religion would give every individual  the same prescription&lt;br&gt;&#xA;for all time and space.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we believe their is a sort of&#xA;formula for doing human&#xA;and we check with the external reality&#xA;on how to behave&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we celebrate and acknowledge our differences&#xA;in appearance, and beliefs,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(religion)&#xA;the idea that where we came from&#xA;and our age does not determine our differences&#xA;but&#xA;and instead makes up a portion of our differences,&#xA;and rather physical appearance gets more credit&#xA;as a differences than age&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
